<doxygenconfig>
  <header>
    <docs doxywizard='0' doxyfile='0'>
      <![CDATA[
/*
 *
 *
 *
 * Copyright (C) 1997-2015 by Dimitri van Heesch.
 *
 * Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software and its
 * documentation under the terms of the GNU General Public License is hereby
 * granted. No representations are made about the suitability of this software
 * for any purpose. It is provided "as is" without express or implied warranty.
 * See the GNU General Public License for more details.
 *
 * Documents produced by Doxygen are derivative works derived from the
 * input used in their production; they are not affected by this license.
 *
 */
/*! \page config Configuration

\tableofcontents
\section config_format Format

A configuration file is a free-form ASCII text file with a structure
that is similar to that of a \c Makefile, with the default name \c Doxyfile. It is
parsed by \c doxygen. The file may contain tabs and newlines for
formatting purposes. The statements in the file are case-sensitive.

The configuration file essentially consists of a list of assignment statements.
Each statement consists of a \c TAG_NAME written in capitals,
followed by the equal sign (<code>=</code>) and one or more values. If the same tag
is assigned more than once, the last assignment overwrites any earlier
assignment. For tags that take a list as their argument,
the <code>+=</code> operator can be used instead of <code>=</code> to append
new values to the list. Values are sequences of non-blanks. If the value should
contain one or more blanks it must be surrounded by quotes (<code>&quot;...&quot;</code>).
Multiple lines can be concatenated by inserting a backslash (\c \\)
as the last non-whitespace character of a line.

Comments begin with the hash character (\c \#) and end at the end of the line.
Comments may be placed anywhere within the file (except within quotes).
Comments beginning with two hash characters (\c \#\#) are kept while updating
the configuration file when they are placed in front of a \c TAG_NAME, or
at the beginning or end of the configuration file.

Environment variables can be expanded using the pattern <code>\$(ENV_VARIABLE_NAME)</code>.
A small example:
\verbatim
DOT_PATH      = $(YOUR_DOT_PATH)
\endverbatim

You can also include part of a configuration file from another configuration
file using a <code>\@INCLUDE</code> tag as follows:
\verbatim
@INCLUDE = config_file_name
\endverbatim
The include file is searched in the current working directory. You can
also specify a list of directories that should be searched before looking
in the current working directory. Do this by putting a <code>\@INCLUDE_PATH</code> tag
with these paths before the <code>\@INCLUDE</code> tag, e.g.:
\verbatim
@INCLUDE_PATH = my_config_dir
\endverbatim

The configuration options can be divided into several categories.
Below is an alphabetical index of the tags that are recognized
followed by the descriptions of the tags grouped by category.
]]>
    </docs>
    <docs doxywizard='0' documentation='0'>
      <![CDATA[
This file describes the settings to be used by the documentation system
Doxygen (www.doxygen.org) for a project.
<br>
All text after a double hash (##) is considered a comment and is placed
in front of the TAG it is preceding.<br>
All text after a single hash (#) is considered a comment and will be ignored.
The format is:
\verbatim
      TAG = value [value, ...]
\endverbatim
For lists, items can also be appended using:
\verbatim
      TAG += value [value, ...]
\endverbatim
Values that contain spaces should be placed between quotes (\" \").
<br>
Note:<br>
Use Doxygen to compare the used configuration file with the template configuration file:
\verbatim
      doxygen -x [configFile]
\endverbatim
Use Doxygen to compare the used configuration file with the template configuration file
without replacing the environment variables or CMake type replacement variables:
\verbatim
      doxygen -x_noenv [configFile]
\endverbatim
]]>
    </docs>
  </header>
  <footer>
    <docs doxywizard='0' doxyfile='0'>
      <![CDATA[
\section config_examples Examples

Suppose you have a simple project consisting of two files: a source file
\c example.cc and a header file \c example.h.
Then a minimal configuration file is as simple as:
\verbatim
INPUT            = example.cc example.h
\endverbatim

Assuming the example makes use of Qt classes and \c perl is located
in <code>/usr/bin</code>, a more realistic configuration file would be:
\verbatim
PROJECT_NAME     = Example
INPUT            = example.cc example.h
WARNINGS         = YES
TAGFILES         = qt.tag
SEARCHENGINE     = NO
\endverbatim

To generate the documentation for the
<a href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/qdbttabular/">QdbtTabular</a> package
I have used the following configuration file:
\verbatim
PROJECT_NAME     = QdbtTabular
OUTPUT_DIRECTORY = html
WARNINGS         = YES
INPUT            = examples/examples.doc src
FILE_PATTERNS    = *.cc *.h
INCLUDE_PATH     = examples
TAGFILES         = qt.tag
SEARCHENGINE     = YES
\endverbatim

To regenerate the Qt-1.44 documentation from the sources, you could use the
following configuration file:
\verbatim
PROJECT_NAME         = Qt
OUTPUT_DIRECTORY     = qt_docs
HIDE_UNDOC_MEMBERS   = YES
HIDE_UNDOC_CLASSES   = YES
ENABLE_PREPROCESSING = YES
MACRO_EXPANSION      = YES
EXPAND_ONLY_PREDEF   = YES
SEARCH_INCLUDES      = YES
FULL_PATH_NAMES      = YES
STRIP_FROM_PATH      = $(QTDIR)/
PREDEFINED           = USE_TEMPLATECLASS Q_EXPORT= \
                       QArrayT:=QArray \
                       QListT:=QList \
                       QDictT:=QDict \
                       QQueueT:=QQueue \
                       QVectorT:=QVector \
                       QPtrDictT:=QPtrDict \
                       QIntDictT:=QIntDict \
                       QStackT:=QStack \
                       QDictIteratorT:=QDictIterator \
                       QListIteratorT:=QListIterator \
                       QCacheT:=QCache \
                       QCacheIteratorT:=QCacheIterator \
                       QIntCacheT:=QIntCache \
                       QIntCacheIteratorT:=QIntCacheIterator \
                       QIntDictIteratorT:=QIntDictIterator \
                       QPtrDictIteratorT:=QPtrDictIterator
INPUT                = $(QTDIR)/doc \
                       $(QTDIR)/src/widgets \
                       $(QTDIR)/src/kernel \
                       $(QTDIR)/src/dialogs \
                       $(QTDIR)/src/tools
FILE_PATTERNS        = *.cpp *.h q*.doc
INCLUDE_PATH         = $(QTDIR)/include
RECURSIVE            = YES
\endverbatim

For the Qt-2.1 sources I recommend to use the following settings:
\verbatim
PROJECT_NAME          = Qt
PROJECT_NUMBER        = 2.1
HIDE_UNDOC_MEMBERS    = YES
HIDE_UNDOC_CLASSES    = YES
SOURCE_BROWSER        = YES
INPUT                 = $(QTDIR)/src
FILE_PATTERNS         = *.cpp *.h q*.doc
RECURSIVE             = YES
EXCLUDE_PATTERNS      = *codec.cpp moc_* */compat/* */3rdparty/*
ALPHABETICAL_INDEX    = YES
IGNORE_PREFIX         = Q
ENABLE_PREPROCESSING  = YES
MACRO_EXPANSION       = YES
INCLUDE_PATH          = $(QTDIR)/include
PREDEFINED            = Q_PROPERTY(x)= \
                        Q_OVERRIDE(x)= \
                        Q_EXPORT= \
                        Q_ENUMS(x)= \
                        "QT_STATIC_CONST=static const " \
                        _WS_X11_ \
                        INCLUDE_MENUITEM_DEF
EXPAND_ONLY_PREDEF    = YES
EXPAND_AS_DEFINED     = Q_OBJECT_FAKE Q_OBJECT ACTIVATE_SIGNAL_WITH_PARAM \
                        Q_VARIANT_AS
\endverbatim

Here Doxygen's preprocessor is used to substitute some
macro names that are normally substituted by the C preprocessor,
but without doing full macro expansion.


\htmlonly
Go to the <a href="commands.html">next</a> section or return to the
 <a href="index.html">index</a>.
\endhtmlonly

*/
]]>
    </docs>
  </footer>

  <group name='Project' docs='Project related configuration options'>
    <option type='string' id='DOXYFILE_ENCODING' format='string' defval='UTF-8'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag specifies the encoding used for all characters in the configuration file that
 follow. The default is UTF-8 which is also the encoding used for all text before
 the first occurrence of this tag. Doxygen uses \c libiconv (or the iconv built into
 \c libc) for the transcoding. See https://www.gnu.org/software/libiconv/ for the list of
 possible encodings.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='PROJECT_NAME' format='string' defval='My Project'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c PROJECT_NAME tag is a single word (or a sequence of words
 surrounded by double-quotes, unless you are using Doxywizard) that should identify the project for which the
 documentation is generated. This name is used in the title of most
 generated pages and in a few other places.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='PROJECT_NUMBER' format='string' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c PROJECT_NUMBER tag can be used to enter a project or revision number.
 This could be handy for archiving the generated documentation or
 if some version control system is used.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='PROJECT_BRIEF' format='string' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Using the \c PROJECT_BRIEF tag one can provide an optional one line description
 for a project that appears at the top of each page and should give viewers
 a quick idea about the purpose of the project. Keep the description short.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>

    <option type='string' id='PROJECT_LOGO' format='image' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 With the \c PROJECT_LOGO tag one can specify a logo or an icon that is
 included in the documentation. The maximum height of the logo should not
 exceed 55 pixels and the maximum width should not exceed 200 pixels.
 Doxygen will copy the logo to the output directory.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='PROJECT_ICON' format='image' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 With the \c PROJECT_ICON tag one can specify an icon that is
 included in the tabs when the HTML document is shown.
 Doxygen will copy the logo to the output directory.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='OUTPUT_DIRECTORY' format='dir' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c OUTPUT_DIRECTORY tag is used to specify the (relative or absolute)
 path into which the generated documentation will be written.
 If a relative path is entered, it will be relative to the location
 where Doxygen was started. If left blank the current directory will be used.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='CREATE_SUBDIRS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c CREATE_SUBDIRS tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will create
 up to 4096 sub-directories (in 2 levels) under the output directory of each output
 format and will distribute the generated files over these directories.
 Enabling this option can be useful when feeding Doxygen a huge amount of source
 files, where putting all generated files in the same directory would otherwise
 cause performance problems for the file system.
 Adapt \c CREATE_SUBDIRS_LEVEL to control the number of sub-directories.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='CREATE_SUBDIRS_LEVEL' minval='0' maxval='8' defval='8'
            depends='CREATE_SUBDIRS'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Controls the number of sub-directories that will be created when \c CREATE_SUBDIRS tag
 is set to \c YES. Level 0 represents 16 directories, and every level increment
 doubles the number of directories, resulting in 4096 directories at level 8 which is the
 default and also the maximum value. The sub-directories are organized in 2 levels, the first
 level always has a fixed number of 16 directories.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='ALLOW_UNICODE_NAMES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c ALLOW_UNICODE_NAMES tag is set to \c YES,
 Doxygen will allow non-ASCII characters to appear in the names of generated files.
 If set to \c NO, non-ASCII characters will be escaped, for example _xE3_x81_x84
 will be used for Unicode U+3044.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='OUTPUT_LANGUAGE' defval='English'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c OUTPUT_LANGUAGE tag is used to specify the language in which all
 documentation generated by Doxygen is written. Doxygen will use this
 information to generate all constant output in the proper language.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name='Afrikaans'/>
      <value name='Arabic'/>
      <value name='Armenian'/>
      <value name='Brazilian'/>
      <value name='Bulgarian'/>
      <value name='Catalan'/>
      <value name='Chinese'/>
      <value name='Chinese-Traditional'/>
      <value name='Croatian'/>
      <value name='Czech'/>
      <value name='Danish'/>
      <value name='Dutch'/>
      <value name='English' desc='(United States)'/>
      <value name='Esperanto'/>
      <value name='Farsi' desc='(Persian)'/>
      <value name='Finnish'/>
      <value name='French'/>
      <value name='German'/>
      <value name='Greek'/>
      <value name='Hindi'/>
      <value name='Hungarian'/>
      <value name='Indonesian'/>
      <value name='Italian'/>
      <value name='Japanese'/>
      <value name='Japanese-en' desc='(Japanese with English messages)'/>
      <value name='Korean'/>
      <value name='Korean-en' desc='(Korean with English messages)'/>
      <value name='Latvian'/>
      <value name='Lithuanian'/>
      <value name='Macedonian'/>
      <value name='Norwegian'/>
      <value name='Persian' desc='(Farsi)'/>
      <value name='Polish'/>
      <value name='Portuguese'/>
      <value name='Romanian'/>
      <value name='Russian'/>
      <value name='Serbian'/>
      <value name='Serbian-Cyrillic'/>
      <value name='Slovak'/>
      <value name='Slovene'/>
      <value name='Spanish'/>
      <value name='Swedish'/>
      <value name='Turkish'/>
      <value name='Ukrainian'/>
      <value name='Vietnamese'/>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='BRIEF_MEMBER_DESC' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c BRIEF_MEMBER_DESC tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 include brief member descriptions after the members that are listed in
 the file and class documentation (similar to \c Javadoc).
 Set to \c NO to disable this.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='REPEAT_BRIEF' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c REPEAT_BRIEF tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 prepend the brief description of a member or function before the detailed
 description
 <br>Note:
 If both \ref cfg_hide_undoc_members "HIDE_UNDOC_MEMBERS" and
 \ref cfg_brief_member_desc "BRIEF_MEMBER_DESC" are set to \c NO, the
 brief descriptions will be completely suppressed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='ABBREVIATE_BRIEF' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag implements a quasi-intelligent brief description abbreviator
 that is used to form the text in various listings. Each string
 in this list, if found as the leading text of the brief description, will be
 stripped from the text and the result, after processing the whole list, is used
 as the annotated text. Otherwise, the brief description is used as-is. If left
 blank, the following values are used (`$name` is automatically replaced with the
 name of the entity):
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name='The $name class'/>
      <value name='The $name widget'/>
      <value name='The $name file'/>
      <value name='is'/>
      <value name='provides'/>
      <value name='specifies'/>
      <value name='contains'/>
      <value name='represents'/>
      <value name='a'/>
      <value name='an'/>
      <value name='the'/>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='ALWAYS_DETAILED_SEC' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c ALWAYS_DETAILED_SEC and \ref cfg_repeat_brief "REPEAT_BRIEF" tags
 are both set to \c YES then
 Doxygen will generate a detailed section even if there is only a brief
 description.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INLINE_INHERITED_MEMB' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c INLINE_INHERITED_MEMB tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will show all inherited
 members of a class in the documentation of that class as if those members were
 ordinary class members. Constructors, destructors and assignment operators of
 the base classes will not be shown.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='FULL_PATH_NAMES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c FULL_PATH_NAMES tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will prepend the full
 path before files name in the file list and in the header files. If set
 to \c NO the shortest path that makes the file name unique will be used
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='STRIP_FROM_PATH' format='dir' depends='FULL_PATH_NAMES'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c STRIP_FROM_PATH tag
 can be used to strip a user-defined part of the path. Stripping is
 only done if one of the specified strings matches the left-hand part of the
 path. The tag can be used to show relative paths in the file list.
 If left blank the directory from which Doxygen is run is used as the
 path to strip.
 <br>Note that you can specify absolute paths here, but also
 relative paths, which will be relative from the directory where Doxygen is
 started.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='STRIP_FROM_INC_PATH' format='dir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c STRIP_FROM_INC_PATH tag can be used to strip a user-defined part of
 the path mentioned in the documentation of a class, which tells
 the reader which header file to include in order to use a class.
 If left blank only the name of the header file containing the class
 definition is used. Otherwise one should specify the list of include paths that
 are normally passed to the compiler using the `-I` flag.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHORT_NAMES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SHORT_NAMES tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will generate much shorter
 (but less readable) file names. This can be useful if your file system
 doesn't support long names like on DOS, Mac, or CD-ROM.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='JAVADOC_AUTOBRIEF' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  If the \c JAVADOC_AUTOBRIEF tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
  will interpret the first line (until the first dot) of a Javadoc-style
  comment as the brief description. If set to \c NO, the
  Javadoc-style will behave just like regular Qt-style comments
  (thus requiring an explicit \ref cmdbrief "\@brief" command for a brief description.)
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='JAVADOC_BANNER' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  If the \c JAVADOC_BANNER tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
  will interpret a line such as \verbatim /***************\endverbatim as being the
  beginning of a Javadoc-style comment "banner". If set to \c NO, the
  Javadoc-style will behave just like regular comments and it will
  not be interpreted by Doxygen.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='QT_AUTOBRIEF' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  If the \c QT_AUTOBRIEF tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
  will interpret the first line (until the first dot) of a Qt-style
  comment as the brief description. If set to \c NO, the
  Qt-style will behave just like regular Qt-style comments (thus
  requiring an explicit \ref cmdbrief "\\brief" command for a brief description.)
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='MULTILINE_CPP_IS_BRIEF' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  The \c MULTILINE_CPP_IS_BRIEF tag can be set to \c YES to make Doxygen
  treat a multi-line C++ special comment block (i.e. a block of \c //! or \c ///
  comments) as a brief description. This used to be the default behavior.
  The new default is to treat a multi-line C++ comment block as a detailed
  description. Set this tag to \c YES if you prefer the old behavior instead.
  <br>Note that setting this tag to \c YES also means that rational rose comments
  are not recognized any more.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='PYTHON_DOCSTRING' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  By default Python docstrings are displayed as preformatted text
  and Doxygen's special commands cannot be used. By setting \c PYTHON_DOCSTRING to
  \c NO the Doxygen's special commands can be used and the contents of the docstring
  documentation blocks is shown as Doxygen documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INHERIT_DOCS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c INHERIT_DOCS tag is set to \c YES then an undocumented
 member inherits the documentation from any documented member that it
 re-implements.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SEPARATE_MEMBER_PAGES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SEPARATE_MEMBER_PAGES tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will produce
 a new page for each member. If set to \c NO, the documentation of a member will
 be part of the file/class/namespace that contains it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='TAB_SIZE' minval='1' maxval='16' defval='4'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c TAB_SIZE tag can be used to set the number of spaces in a tab.
 Doxygen uses this value to replace tabs by spaces in code fragments.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='ALIASES' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag can be used to specify a number of aliases that act
 as commands in the documentation. An alias has the form:
\verbatim
 name=value
\endverbatim
 For example adding
\verbatim
 "sideeffect=@par Side Effects:^^"
\endverbatim
 will allow you to
 put the command \c \\sideeffect (or \c \@sideeffect) in the documentation, which
 will result in a user-defined paragraph with heading "Side Effects:".
 Note that you cannot put \ref cmdn "\\n"'s in the value part of an alias to insert newlines
 (in the resulting output).
 You can put `^^` in the value part of an alias to insert a newline as if
 a physical newline was in the original file.
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxyfile='0' documentation='0'>
<![CDATA[
 When you need a literal `{` or `}` or `,` in the value part of an alias you have to
 escape them by means of a backslash, this can lead to conflicts with the
 commands \c \\{ and \c \\} for these it is advised to use the version \c @{ and \c @} or
 use a double escape (\c \\\\{ and \c \\\\})
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxywizard='0' documentation='0'>
<![CDATA[
 When you need a literal `{` or `}` or `,` in the value part of an alias you have to
 escape them by means of a backslash (\c \\), this can lead to conflicts with the
 commands \c \\{ and \c \\} for these it is advised to use the version \c @{ and \c @} or
 use a double escape (\c \\\\{ and \c \\\\})
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxyfile='0' doxywizard='0'>
<![CDATA[
 When you need a literal `{` or `}` or `,` in the value part of an alias you have to
 escape them by means of a backslash (`\`), this can lead to conflicts with the
 commands \c \\{ and \c \\} for these it is advised to use the version \c @@{ and \c @@} or
 use a double escape (\c \\\\{ and \c \\\\})
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_FOR_C' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_FOR_C tag to \c YES if your project consists
 of C sources only. Doxygen will then generate output that is more tailored
 for C. For instance, some of the names that are used will be different.
 The list of all members will be omitted, etc.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_JAVA' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_JAVA tag to \c YES if your project consists of Java or
 Python sources only. Doxygen will then generate output that is more tailored
 for that language. For instance, namespaces will be presented as packages,
 qualified scopes will look different, etc.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='OPTIMIZE_FOR_FORTRAN' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c OPTIMIZE_FOR_FORTRAN tag to \c YES if your project consists of Fortran
 sources. Doxygen will then generate output that is tailored for Fortran.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_VHDL' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_VHDL tag to \c YES if your project consists of VHDL
 sources. Doxygen will then generate output that is tailored for VHDL.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_SLICE' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c OPTIMIZE_OUTPUT_SLICE tag to \c YES if your project consists of Slice
 sources only. Doxygen will then generate output that is more tailored
 for that language. For instance, namespaces will be presented as modules,
 types will be separated into more groups, etc.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXTENSION_MAPPING' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Doxygen selects the parser to use depending on the extension of the files it parses.
 With this tag you can assign which parser to use for a given extension.
 Doxygen has a built-in mapping, but you can override or extend it using this tag.
 The format is <code>ext=language</code>, where \c ext is a file extension, and language is one of
 the parsers supported by Doxygen: IDL, Java, JavaScript, Csharp (C#), C, C++, Lex, D, PHP,
 md (Markdown), Objective-C, Python, Slice, VHDL, Fortran (fixed format Fortran: FortranFixed,
 free formatted Fortran: FortranFree, unknown formatted Fortran: Fortran. In
 the later case the parser tries to guess whether the code is fixed or free
 formatted code, this is the default for Fortran type files).

 For instance to make Doxygen treat
 <code>.inc</code> files as Fortran files (default is PHP), and <code>.f</code> files as C (default is Fortran),
 use: `inc=Fortran f=C`.

 <br>Note: For files without extension you can use `no_extension` as a placeholder.
 <br>Note that for custom extensions you also need to set \ref cfg_file_patterns "FILE_PATTERNS" otherwise the
 files are not read by Doxygen. When specifying `no_extension` you should add `*`
 to the \ref cfg_file_patterns "FILE_PATTERNS".
 <br>Note see also the list of \ref default_file_extension_mapping "default file extension mappings".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='MARKDOWN_SUPPORT' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c MARKDOWN_SUPPORT tag is enabled then Doxygen pre-processes all
 comments according to the Markdown format, which allows for more readable
 documentation. See https://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/ for details.
 The output of markdown processing is further processed by Doxygen, so you
 can mix Doxygen, HTML, and XML commands with Markdown formatting.
 Disable only in case of backward compatibilities issues.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='TOC_INCLUDE_HEADINGS' minval='0' maxval='99' defval='6' depends='MARKDOWN_SUPPORT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When the \c TOC_INCLUDE_HEADINGS tag is set to a non-zero value, all headings
 up to that level are automatically included in the table of contents, even if
 they do not have an id attribute.
 \note This feature currently applies only to Markdown headings.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='MARKDOWN_ID_STYLE' defval='DOXYGEN' depends='MARKDOWN_SUPPORT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MARKDOWN_ID_STYLE tag can be used to specify the algorithm used to generate identifiers for the Markdown headings.
 Note: Every identifier is unique.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="DOXYGEN" desc="use a fixed 'autotoc_md' string followed by a sequence number starting at 0"/>
      <value name="GITHUB" desc="use the lower case version of title with any whitespace replaced by '-' and punctuation characters removed"/>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='AUTOLINK_SUPPORT' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When enabled Doxygen tries to link words that correspond to documented classes,
 or namespaces to their corresponding documentation. Such a link can be
 prevented in individual cases by putting a \c % sign in front of the word or
 globally by setting \c AUTOLINK_SUPPORT to \c NO.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='BUILTIN_STL_SUPPORT' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If you use STL classes (i.e. `std::string`, `std::vector`, etc.) but do not want to
 include (a tag file for) the STL sources as input, then you should
 set this tag to \c YES in order to let Doxygen match functions declarations and
 definitions whose arguments contain STL classes (e.g. `func(std::string`); versus
 `func(std::string) {}`). This also makes the inheritance and collaboration
 diagrams that involve STL classes more complete and accurate.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='CPP_CLI_SUPPORT' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If you use Microsoft's C++/CLI language, you should set this option to \c YES to
 enable parsing support.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SIP_SUPPORT' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c SIP_SUPPORT tag to \c YES if your project consists
 of <a href="https://www.riverbankcomputing.com/software">sip</a> sources only.
 Doxygen will parse them like normal C++ but will assume all classes use public
 instead of private inheritance when no explicit protection keyword is present.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='IDL_PROPERTY_SUPPORT' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 For Microsoft's IDL there are \c propget and \c propput attributes to indicate getter
 and setter methods for a property. Setting this option to \c YES
 will make Doxygen to replace the get and set methods by a property in the
 documentation. This will only work if the methods are indeed getting or
 setting a simple type. If this is not the case, or you want to show the
 methods anyway, you should set this option to \c NO.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='DISTRIBUTE_GROUP_DOC' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If member grouping is used in the documentation and the \c DISTRIBUTE_GROUP_DOC
 tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will reuse the documentation of the first
 member in the group (if any) for the other members of the group. By default
 all members of a group must be documented explicitly.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GROUP_NESTED_COMPOUNDS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If one adds a struct or class to a group and this option is enabled, then also
 any nested class or struct is added to the same group. By default this option
 is disabled and one has to add nested compounds explicitly via \ref cmdingroup "\\ingroup".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SUBGROUPING' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c SUBGROUPING tag to \c YES to allow class member groups of
 the same type (for instance a group of public functions) to be put as a
 subgroup of that type (e.g. under the Public Functions section). Set it to
 \c NO to prevent subgrouping. Alternatively, this can be done per class using
 the \ref cmdnosubgrouping "\\nosubgrouping" command.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INLINE_GROUPED_CLASSES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When the \c INLINE_GROUPED_CLASSES tag is set to \c YES, classes, structs and
 unions are shown inside the group in which they are included
 (e.g. using \ref cmdingroup "\\ingroup") instead of on a separate page (for HTML and Man pages)
 or section (for \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ and RTF).
 <br>Note that this feature does not work in
 combination with \ref cfg_separate_member_pages "SEPARATE_MEMBER_PAGES".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INLINE_SIMPLE_STRUCTS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When the \c INLINE_SIMPLE_STRUCTS tag is set to \c YES, structs, classes, and
 unions with only public data fields or simple typedef fields will be shown
 inline in the documentation of the scope in which they are defined (i.e. file,
 namespace, or group documentation), provided this scope is documented. If set
 to \c NO, structs, classes, and unions are shown on a separate
 page (for HTML and Man pages) or section (for \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ and RTF).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='TYPEDEF_HIDES_STRUCT' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When \c TYPEDEF_HIDES_STRUCT tag is enabled, a typedef of a struct, union, or enum
 is documented as struct, union, or enum with the name of the typedef. So
 <code>typedef struct TypeS {} TypeT</code>, will appear in the documentation as a struct
 with name \c TypeT. When disabled the typedef will appear as a member of a file,
 namespace, or class. And the struct will be named \c TypeS. This can typically
 be useful for C code in case the coding convention dictates that all compound
 types are typedef'ed and only the typedef is referenced, never the tag name.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='LOOKUP_CACHE_SIZE' minval='0' maxval='9' defval='0'>
      <!-- be careful when changing these formulas as they are hard coded in the conversion script -->
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The size of the symbol lookup cache can be
 set using \c LOOKUP_CACHE_SIZE. This cache is used to resolve symbols given
 their name and scope. Since this can be an expensive process and often the
 same symbol appears multiple times in the code, Doxygen keeps a cache of
 pre-resolved symbols. If the cache is too small Doxygen will become slower.
 If the cache is too large, memory is wasted. The cache size is given by this
 formula: \f$2^{(16+\mbox{LOOKUP\_CACHE\_SIZE})}\f$. The valid range is 0..9, the default is 0,
 corresponding to a cache size of \f$2^{16} = 65536\f$ symbols.
 At the end of a run Doxygen will report the cache usage and suggest the
 optimal cache size from a speed point of view.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='NUM_PROC_THREADS' defval='1' minval='0' maxval='32'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c NUM_PROC_THREADS specifies the number of threads Doxygen is allowed to use during
 processing. When set to \c 0 Doxygen will based this on the number of cores
 available in the system. You can set it explicitly to a value larger than 0
 to get more control over the balance between CPU load and processing speed.
 At this moment only the input processing can be done using multiple threads.
 Since this is still an experimental feature the default is set to 1,
 which effectively disables parallel processing. Please report any issues you
 encounter.
 Generating dot graphs in parallel is controlled by the \c DOT_NUM_THREADS setting.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='TIMESTAMP' defval='NO'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c TIMESTAMP tag is set different from \c NO then 
 each generated page will contain the date or date and time when the page
 was generated. Setting this to \c NO can help when comparing the output of
 multiple runs.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="YES" />
      <value name="NO" />
      <value name="DATETIME" />
      <value name="DATE" />
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Build' docs='Build related configuration options'>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_ALL' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTRACT_ALL tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will assume all
 entities in documentation are documented, even if no documentation was
 available. Private class members and static file members will be hidden
 unless the \ref cfg_extract_private "EXTRACT_PRIVATE" respectively
 \ref cfg_extract_static "EXTRACT_STATIC" tags are set to \c YES.

 \note This will also disable the warnings about undocumented members
 that are normally produced when \ref cfg_warnings "WARNINGS" is
 set to \c YES.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_PRIVATE' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTRACT_PRIVATE tag is set to \c YES, all private members of a
 class will be included in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_PRIV_VIRTUAL' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTRACT_PRIV_VIRTUAL tag is set to \c YES, documented private
 virtual methods of a class will be included in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_PACKAGE' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTRACT_PACKAGE tag is set to \c YES, all members with package
 or internal scope will be included in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_STATIC' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTRACT_STATIC tag is set to \c YES, all static members of a file
 will be included in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_LOCAL_CLASSES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTRACT_LOCAL_CLASSES tag is set to \c YES, classes (and structs)
 defined locally in source files will be included in the documentation.
 If set to \c NO, only classes defined in header files are included. Does not
 have any effect for Java sources.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_LOCAL_METHODS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This flag is only useful for Objective-C code. If set to \c YES, local
 methods, which are defined in the implementation section but not in
 the interface are included in the documentation.
 If set to \c NO, only methods in the interface are included.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTRACT_ANON_NSPACES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If this flag is set to \c YES, the members of anonymous namespaces will be extracted
 and appear in the documentation as a namespace called 'anonymous_namespace{file}',
 where file will be replaced with the base name of the file that contains the anonymous
 namespace. By default anonymous namespace are hidden.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='RESOLVE_UNNAMED_PARAMS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If this flag is set to \c YES, the name of an unnamed parameter in a declaration will be
 determined by the corresponding definition. By default unnamed parameters remain unnamed
 in the output.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_UNDOC_MEMBERS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HIDE_UNDOC_MEMBERS tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will hide all
 undocumented members inside documented classes or files.
 If set to \c NO these members will be included in the
 various overviews, but no documentation section is generated.
 This option has no effect if \ref cfg_extract_all "EXTRACT_ALL" is enabled.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_UNDOC_CLASSES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HIDE_UNDOC_CLASSES tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will hide all
 undocumented classes that are normally visible in the class hierarchy.
 If set to \c NO, these classes will be included in the
 various overviews. This option will also hide undocumented C++ concepts
 if enabled.
 This option has no effect if \ref cfg_extract_all "EXTRACT_ALL" is enabled.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_UNDOC_NAMESPACES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HIDE_UNDOC_NAMESPACES tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will hide all
 undocumented namespaces that are normally visible in the namespace hierarchy.
 If set to \c NO, these namespaces will be included in the
 various overviews.
 This option has no effect if \ref cfg_extract_all "EXTRACT_ALL" is enabled.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_FRIEND_COMPOUNDS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HIDE_FRIEND_COMPOUNDS tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will hide all
 friend declarations.
 If set to \c NO, these declarations will be included in the
 documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_IN_BODY_DOCS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HIDE_IN_BODY_DOCS tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will hide any
 documentation blocks found inside the body of a function.
 If set to \c NO, these blocks will be appended to the
 function's detailed documentation block.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INTERNAL_DOCS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c INTERNAL_DOCS tag determines if documentation
 that is typed after a \ref cmdinternal "\\internal" command is included. If the tag is set
 to \c NO then the documentation will be excluded.
 Set it to \c YES to include the internal documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='CASE_SENSE_NAMES' defval='SYSTEM'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 With the correct setting of option \c CASE_SENSE_NAMES Doxygen will better be able to match the
 capabilities of the underlying filesystem.

 In case the filesystem is case sensitive (i.e. it supports files in the same directory
 whose names only differ in casing), the option must be set to \c YES to properly deal with such files
 in case they appear in the input.

 For filesystems that are not case sensitive the option should be set to \c NO to properly
 deal with output files written for symbols that only differ in casing, such as for two classes,
 one named \c CLASS and the other named \c Class, and to also support references to files without
 having to specify the exact matching casing.

 On Windows (including Cygwin) and macOS, users should typically set this option to \c NO,
 whereas on Linux or other Unix flavors it should typically be set to \c YES.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="SYSTEM" />
      <value name="NO"/>
      <value name="YES" />
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_SCOPE_NAMES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HIDE_SCOPE_NAMES tag is set to \c NO then Doxygen
 will show members with their full class and namespace scopes in the
 documentation. If set to \c YES, the scope will be hidden.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_COMPOUND_REFERENCE' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HIDE_COMPOUND_REFERENCE tag is set to \c NO (default) then
 Doxygen will append additional text to a page's title, such as Class Reference.
 If set to \c YES the compound reference will be hidden.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHOW_HEADERFILE' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SHOW_HEADERFILE tag is set to \c YES then the documentation
 for a class will show which file needs to be included to use the class.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHOW_INCLUDE_FILES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SHOW_INCLUDE_FILES tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
 will put a list of the files that are included by a file in the documentation
 of that file.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHOW_GROUPED_MEMB_INC' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SHOW_GROUPED_MEMB_INC tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
 will add for each grouped member an include statement to the documentation,
 telling the reader which file to include in order to use the member.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='FORCE_LOCAL_INCLUDES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c FORCE_LOCAL_INCLUDES tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
 will list include files with double quotes in the documentation
 rather than with sharp brackets.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INLINE_INFO' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c INLINE_INFO tag is set to \c YES then a tag [inline]
 is inserted in the documentation for inline members.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SORT_MEMBER_DOCS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SORT_MEMBER_DOCS tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
 will sort the (detailed) documentation of file and class members
 alphabetically by member name. If set to \c NO, the members will appear in
 declaration order.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SORT_BRIEF_DOCS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SORT_BRIEF_DOCS tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will sort the
 brief descriptions of file, namespace and class members alphabetically
 by member name. If set to \c NO, the members will appear in
 declaration order. Note that this will also influence the order of the
 classes in the class list.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SORT_MEMBERS_CTORS_1ST' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SORT_MEMBERS_CTORS_1ST tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
 will sort the (brief and detailed) documentation of class members so that
 constructors and destructors are listed first. If set to \c NO
 the constructors will appear in the respective orders defined by
 \ref cfg_sort_brief_docs "SORT_BRIEF_DOCS" and \ref cfg_sort_member_docs "SORT_MEMBER_DOCS".
 \note If \ref cfg_sort_brief_docs "SORT_BRIEF_DOCS" is set to \c NO this option is ignored for
       sorting brief member documentation.
 \note If \ref cfg_sort_member_docs "SORT_MEMBER_DOCS" is set to \c NO this option is ignored for
       sorting detailed member documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SORT_GROUP_NAMES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SORT_GROUP_NAMES tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will sort the
 hierarchy of group names into alphabetical order. If set to \c NO
 the group names will appear in their defined order.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SORT_BY_SCOPE_NAME' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SORT_BY_SCOPE_NAME tag is set to \c YES, the class list will be
 sorted by fully-qualified names, including namespaces. If set to
 \c NO, the class list will be sorted only by class name,
 not including the namespace part.
 \note This option is not very useful if \ref cfg_hide_scope_names "HIDE_SCOPE_NAMES" is set to \c YES.
 \note This option applies only to the class list, not to the
       alphabetical list.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='STRICT_PROTO_MATCHING' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c STRICT_PROTO_MATCHING option is enabled and Doxygen fails to
 do proper type resolution of all parameters of a function it will reject a
 match between the prototype and the implementation of a member function even
 if there is only one candidate or it is obvious which candidate to choose
 by doing a simple string match. By disabling \c STRICT_PROTO_MATCHING Doxygen
 will still accept a match between prototype and implementation in such cases.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_TODOLIST' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c GENERATE_TODOLIST tag can be used to enable (\c YES) or
 disable (\c NO) the todo list. This list is created by
 putting \ref cmdtodo "\\todo" commands in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_TESTLIST' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c GENERATE_TESTLIST tag can be used to enable (\c YES) or
 disable (\c NO) the test list. This list is created by
 putting \ref cmdtest "\\test" commands in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_BUGLIST' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c GENERATE_BUGLIST tag can be used to enable (\c YES) or
 disable (\c NO) the bug list. This list is created by
 putting \ref cmdbug "\\bug" commands in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_DEPRECATEDLIST' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c GENERATE_DEPRECATEDLIST tag can be used to enable (\c YES) or
 disable (\c NO) the deprecated list. This list is created by
 putting \ref cmddeprecated "\\deprecated"
 commands in the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='ENABLED_SECTIONS' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c ENABLED_SECTIONS tag can be used to enable conditional
 documentation sections, marked by \ref cmdif "\\if" \<section_label\> ...
 \ref cmdendif "\\endif" and \ref cmdcond "\\cond" \<section_label\> ...
 \ref cmdendcond "\\endcond" blocks.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='MAX_INITIALIZER_LINES' minval='0' maxval='10000' defval='30'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MAX_INITIALIZER_LINES tag determines the maximum number of lines
 that the initial value of a variable or macro / define can have for it to appear in
 the documentation. If the initializer
 consists of more lines than specified here it will be hidden. Use a value
 of 0 to hide initializers completely. The appearance of the value of
 individual variables and macros / defines can be controlled using \ref cmdshowinitializer "\\showinitializer"
 or \ref cmdhideinitializer "\\hideinitializer" command in the documentation regardless of this setting.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHOW_USED_FILES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c SHOW_USED_FILES tag to \c NO to disable the list of files generated
 at the bottom of the documentation of classes and structs. If set to \c YES, the
 list will mention the files that were used to generate the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHOW_FILES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c SHOW_FILES tag to \c NO to disable the generation of the Files page.
 This will remove the Files entry from the Quick Index and from the
 Folder Tree View (if specified).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHOW_NAMESPACES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c SHOW_NAMESPACES tag to \c NO to disable the generation of the
 Namespaces page. This will remove the Namespaces entry from the Quick Index
 and from the Folder Tree View (if specified).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='FILE_VERSION_FILTER' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c FILE_VERSION_FILTER tag can be used to specify a program or script that
 Doxygen should invoke to get the current version for each file (typically from the
 version control system). Doxygen will invoke the program by executing (via
 <code>popen()</code>) the command <code>command input-file</code>, where \c command is
 the value of the \c FILE_VERSION_FILTER tag, and \c input-file is the name
 of an input file provided by Doxygen.
 Whatever the program writes to standard output is used as the file version.
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxywizard='0' doxyfile='0'>
<![CDATA[
<br>
<br>
Example of using a shell script as a filter for Unix:
\verbatim
 FILE_VERSION_FILTER = "/bin/sh versionfilter.sh"
\endverbatim
<br>
Example shell script for CVS:
\verbatim
#!/bin/sh
cvs status $1 | sed -n 's/^[ \]*Working revision:[ \t]*\([0-9][0-9\.]*\).*/\1/p'
\endverbatim
<br>
Example shell script for Subversion:
\verbatim
#!/bin/sh
svn stat -v $1 | sed -n 's/^[ A-Z?\*|!]\{1,15\}/r/;s/ \{1,15\}/\/r/;s/ .*//p'
\endverbatim
<br>
Example filter for ClearCase:
\verbatim
FILE_VERSION_FILTER = "cleartool desc -fmt \%Vn"
\endverbatim
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs documentation='0'>
<![CDATA[
 For an example see the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LAYOUT_FILE' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LAYOUT_FILE tag can be used to specify a layout file which will be parsed by
 Doxygen. The layout file controls the global structure of the generated output files
 in an output format independent way. To create the layout file that represents
 Doxygen's defaults, run Doxygen with the `-l` option. You can optionally specify a
 file name after the option, if omitted \c DoxygenLayout.xml will be used as the name
 of the layout file.
 See also section \ref layout for information.
 <br>Note that if you run Doxygen from a directory containing
 a file called \c DoxygenLayout.xml, Doxygen will parse it automatically even if
 the \c LAYOUT_FILE tag is left empty.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='CITE_BIB_FILES' format='file'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c CITE_BIB_FILES tag can be used to specify one or more \c bib files
 containing the reference definitions. This must be a list of <code>.bib</code> files. The
 <code>.bib</code> extension is automatically appended if omitted. This requires the
 \c bibtex tool to be installed. See also https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BibTeX for
 more info. For \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ the style of the bibliography can be controlled
 using \ref cfg_latex_bib_style "LATEX_BIB_STYLE".
 To use this feature you need \c bibtex and \c perl available in the search path.
 See also \ref cmdcite "\\cite" for info how to create references.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXTERNAL_TOOL_PATH' format='dir' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c EXTERNAL_TOOL_PATH tag can be used to extend the search path (PATH environment variable)
 so that external tools such as \c latex and \c gs can be found. 
 \note Directories specified with EXTERNAL_TOOL_PATH are added in front of the path already specified by
 the PATH variable, and are added in the order specified.
 \note This option is particularly useful for macOS version 14 (Sonoma) and higher,
 when running Doxygen from Doxywizard, because in this case any user-defined changes to the PATH
 are ignored. A typical example on macOS is to set
\verbatim
EXTERNAL_TOOL_PATH = /Library/TeX/texbin /usr/local/bin
\endverbatim
 together with the standard path, the full search path used by doxygen when launching external tools
 will then become
\verbatim
PATH=/Library/TeX/texbin:/usr/local/bin:/usr/bin:/bin:/usr/sbin:/sbin
\endverbatim
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Messages' docs='Configuration options related to warning and progress messages'>
    <option type='bool' id='QUIET' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c QUIET tag can be used to turn on/off the messages that are generated
 to standard output by Doxygen. If \c QUIET is set to \c YES this implies that the messages are off.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='WARNINGS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c WARNINGS tag can be used to turn on/off the warning messages that are
 generated to standard error (\c stderr) by Doxygen. If \c WARNINGS is set to
 \c YES this implies that the warnings are on.
<br>
 \b Tip: Turn warnings on while writing the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='WARN_IF_UNDOCUMENTED' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c WARN_IF_UNDOCUMENTED tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will generate warnings
 for undocumented members. If \ref cfg_extract_all "EXTRACT_ALL" is set to \c YES then this flag will
 automatically be disabled.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='WARN_IF_DOC_ERROR' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c WARN_IF_DOC_ERROR tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will generate warnings for
 potential errors in the documentation, such as documenting some
 parameters in a documented function twice, or documenting parameters that
 don't exist or using markup commands wrongly.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='WARN_IF_INCOMPLETE_DOC' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If \c WARN_IF_INCOMPLETE_DOC is set to \c YES, Doxygen will warn about
 incomplete function parameter documentation.
 If set to \c NO, Doxygen will accept that some parameters have no
 documentation without warning.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='WARN_NO_PARAMDOC' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This \c WARN_NO_PARAMDOC option can be enabled to get warnings for
 functions that are documented, but have no documentation for their parameters
 or return value. If set to \c NO, Doxygen will only warn about
 wrong parameter documentation, but not about the absence of
 documentation.
 If \ref cfg_extract_all "EXTRACT_ALL" is set to \c YES then this flag will
 automatically be disabled.
 See also \ref cfg_warn_if_incomplete_doc "WARN_IF_INCOMPLETE_DOC"
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='WARN_IF_UNDOC_ENUM_VAL' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If \c WARN_IF_UNDOC_ENUM_VAL option is set to \c YES, Doxygen will warn
 about undocumented enumeration values.
 If set to \c NO, Doxygen will accept undocumented enumeration values.
 If \ref cfg_extract_all "EXTRACT_ALL" is set to \c YES then this flag will
 automatically be disabled.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='WARN_AS_ERROR' defval='NO'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c WARN_AS_ERROR tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will immediately stop
 when a warning is encountered.
 If the \c WARN_AS_ERROR tag is set to \c FAIL_ON_WARNINGS then Doxygen will continue
 running as if \c WARN_AS_ERROR tag is set to \c NO, but at the end of the Doxygen
 process Doxygen will return with a non-zero status.
 If the \c WARN_AS_ERROR tag is set to \c FAIL_ON_WARNINGS_PRINT then Doxygen behaves like
 \c FAIL_ON_WARNINGS but in case no \ref cfg_warn_logfile "WARN_LOGFILE" is defined
 Doxygen will not write the warning messages in between other
 messages but write them at the end of a run, in case a
 \ref cfg_warn_logfile "WARN_LOGFILE" is defined the warning messages will be
 besides being in the defined file also be shown at the end of a run, unless the
 \ref cfg_warn_logfile "WARN_LOGFILE" is defined as `-` i.e. standard output (`stdout`)
 in that case the behavior will remain as with the setting \c FAIL_ON_WARNINGS.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="NO"/>
      <value name="YES" />
      <value name="FAIL_ON_WARNINGS" />
      <value name="FAIL_ON_WARNINGS_PRINT" />
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='WARN_FORMAT' format='string' defval='$file:$line: $text'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c WARN_FORMAT tag determines the format of the warning messages that
 Doxygen can produce. The string should contain the <code>\$file</code>,
 <code>\$line</code>, and <code>\$text</code>
 tags, which will be replaced by the file and line number from which the
 warning originated and the warning text.
 Optionally the format may contain
 <code>$version</code>, which will be replaced by the version of the file (if it could
 be obtained via \ref cfg_file_version_filter "FILE_VERSION_FILTER")

 \sa \ref cfg_warn_line_format "WARN_LINE_FORMAT"
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='WARN_LINE_FORMAT' format='string' defval='at line $line of file $file'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 In the `$text` part of the \ref cfg_warn_format "WARN_FORMAT" command it is
 possible that a reference to a more specific place is given.  To make it easier
 to jump to this place (outside of Doxygen) the user can define a custom
 "cut" / "paste" string.

 Example:
 \verbatim
  WARN_LINE_FORMAT = "'vi $file +$line'"
 \endverbatim

 \sa \ref cfg_warn_format "WARN_FORMAT"
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='WARN_LOGFILE' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c WARN_LOGFILE tag can be used to specify a file to which warning
 and error messages should be written. If left blank the output is written
 to standard error (`stderr`). In case the file specified cannot be opened for
 writing the warning and error messages are written to standard error. When as
 file `-` is specified the warning and error messages are written to standard output
 (`stdout`).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Input' docs='Configuration options related to the input files'>
    <option type='list' id='INPUT' format='filedir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c INPUT tag is used to specify the files and/or directories that contain
 documented source files. You may enter file names like
 \c myfile.cpp or directories like \c /usr/src/myproject.
 Separate the files or directories with spaces. See also
 \ref cfg_file_patterns "FILE_PATTERNS"  and
 \ref cfg_extension_mapping "EXTENSION_MAPPING"

 \note If this tag is empty the current directory is searched.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='INPUT_ENCODING' format='string' defval='UTF-8'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag can be used to specify the character encoding of the source files that
 Doxygen parses. Internally Doxygen uses the UTF-8 encoding.
 Doxygen uses `libiconv` (or the `iconv` built into `libc`) for the transcoding.
 See <a href="https://www.gnu.org/software/libiconv/">the libiconv documentation</a> for
 the list of possible encodings.

 \sa  \ref cfg_input_file_encoding "INPUT_FILE_ENCODING"
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='INPUT_FILE_ENCODING' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag can be used to specify the character encoding of the source files that Doxygen
 parses.
 The \c INPUT_FILE_ENCODING tag can be used to specify character encoding on a per file pattern
 basis. Doxygen will compare the file name with each pattern and apply the
 encoding instead of the default \ref cfg_input_encoding "INPUT_ENCODING" if there is a match.
 The character encodings are a list of the form: pattern=encoding (like `*.php=ISO-8859-1`).

 \sa \ref cfg_input_encoding "INPUT_ENCODING" for further information on supported encodings.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='FILE_PATTERNS' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the value of the \ref cfg_input "INPUT" tag contains directories, you can use the
 \c FILE_PATTERNS tag to specify one or more wildcard patterns
 (like `*.cpp` and `*.h`) to filter out the source-files
 in the directories.<br>
 Note that for custom extensions or not directly supported extensions you also
 need to set \ref cfg_extension_mapping "EXTENSION_MAPPING" for the extension
 otherwise the files are not read by Doxygen.<br>
 Note the list of default checked file patterns might differ from the list of
 \ref default_file_extension_mapping "default file extension mappings".<br>
 If left blank the following patterns are tested:
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name='*.c'/>
      <value name='*.cc'/>
      <value name='*.cxx'/>
      <value name='*.cxxm'/>
      <value name='*.cpp'/>
      <value name='*.cppm'/>
      <value name='*.ccm'/>
      <value name='*.c++'/>
      <value name='*.c++m'/>
      <value name='*.java'/>
      <value name='*.ii'/>
      <value name='*.ixx'/>
      <value name='*.ipp'/>
      <value name='*.i++'/>
      <value name='*.inl'/>
      <value name='*.idl'/>
      <value name='*.ddl'/>
      <value name='*.odl'/>
      <value name='*.h'/>
      <value name='*.hh'/>
      <value name='*.hxx'/>
      <value name='*.hpp'/>
      <value name='*.h++'/>
      <value name='*.ixx'/>
      <value name='*.l'/>
      <value name='*.cs'/>
      <value name='*.d'/>
      <value name='*.php'/>
      <value name='*.php4'/>
      <value name='*.php5'/>
      <value name='*.phtml'/>
      <value name='*.inc'/>
      <value name='*.m'/>
      <value name='*.markdown'/>
      <value name='*.md'/>
      <value name='*.mm'/>
      <value name='*.dox' desc='(to be provided as Doxygen C comment)'/>
      <value name='*.py'/>
      <value name='*.pyw'/>
      <value name='*.f90'/>
      <value name='*.f95'/>
      <value name='*.f03'/>
      <value name='*.f08'/>
      <value name='*.f18'/>
      <value name='*.f'/>
      <value name='*.for'/>
      <value name='*.vhd'/>
      <value name='*.vhdl'/>
      <value name='*.ucf'/>
      <value name='*.qsf'/>
      <value name='*.ice'/>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='RECURSIVE' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c RECURSIVE tag can be used to specify whether or not subdirectories
 should be searched for input files as well.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXCLUDE' format='filedir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c EXCLUDE tag can be used to specify files and/or directories that should be
 excluded from the \ref cfg_input "INPUT" source files. This way you can easily exclude a
 subdirectory from a directory tree whose root is specified with the \ref cfg_input "INPUT" tag.
 <br>Note that relative paths are relative to the directory from which Doxygen is run.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXCLUDE_SYMLINKS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c EXCLUDE_SYMLINKS tag can be used to select whether or not files or directories
 that are symbolic links (a Unix file system feature) are excluded from the input.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXCLUDE_PATTERNS' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the value of the \ref cfg_input "INPUT" tag contains directories, you can use the
 \c EXCLUDE_PATTERNS tag to specify one or more wildcard patterns to exclude
 certain files from those directories.
 <br>Note that the wildcards are matched
 against the file with absolute path, so to exclude all test directories
 for example use the pattern `*``/test/``*`
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXCLUDE_SYMBOLS' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c EXCLUDE_SYMBOLS tag can be used to specify one or more symbol names
 (namespaces, classes, functions, etc.) that should be excluded from the
 output. The symbol name can be a fully qualified name, a word, or if the
 wildcard `*` is used, a substring. Examples: `ANamespace`, `AClass`,
 `ANamespace::AClass`, `ANamespace::*Test`
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXAMPLE_PATH' format='filedir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c EXAMPLE_PATH tag can be used to specify one or more files or
 directories that contain example code fragments that are included (see
 the \ref cmdinclude "\\include" command).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXAMPLE_PATTERNS' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the value of the \ref cfg_example_path "EXAMPLE_PATH" tag contains directories,
 you can use the
 \c EXAMPLE_PATTERNS tag to specify one or more wildcard pattern (like `*.cpp`
 and `*.h`) to filter out the source-files in the directories. If left
 blank all files are included.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name='*' show_docu='NO'/>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXAMPLE_RECURSIVE' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXAMPLE_RECURSIVE tag is set to \c YES then subdirectories will be
 searched for input files to be used with the \ref cmdinclude "\\include" or
 \ref cmddontinclude "\\dontinclude"
 commands irrespective of the value of the \ref cfg_recursive "RECURSIVE" tag.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='IMAGE_PATH' format='filedir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c IMAGE_PATH tag can be used to specify one or more files or
 directories that contain images that are to be included in the
 documentation (see the \ref cmdimage "\\image" command).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='INPUT_FILTER' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c INPUT_FILTER tag can be used to specify a program that Doxygen should
 invoke to filter for each input file. Doxygen will invoke the filter program
 by executing (via <code>popen()</code>) the command:
 <br>
   <code>\<filter\> \<input-file\></code>
 <br>
 where <code>\<filter\></code>
 is the value of the \c INPUT_FILTER tag, and <code>\<input-file\></code> is the name of an
 input file. Doxygen will then use the output that the filter program writes
 to standard output.  If \ref cfg_filter_patterns "FILTER_PATTERNS" is specified, this tag will be ignored.
 <br>Note that the filter must not add or remove lines; it is applied before the
 code is scanned, but not when the output code is generated. If lines are added
 or removed, the anchors will not be placed correctly.
 <br>Note that Doxygen will use the data processed and written to standard output for further processing,
 therefore nothing else, like debug statements or used commands (so in case of a Windows batch file
 always use `@echo OFF`), should be written to standard output.
 <br>Note that for custom extensions or not directly supported extensions you also
 need to set \ref cfg_extension_mapping "EXTENSION_MAPPING" for the extension
 otherwise the files are not properly processed by Doxygen.<br>

]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='FILTER_PATTERNS' format='string'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c FILTER_PATTERNS tag can be used to specify filters on a per file pattern
 basis. Doxygen will compare the file name with each pattern and apply the
 filter if there is a match. The filters are a list of the form:
 pattern=filter (like `*.cpp=my_cpp_filter`). See \ref cfg_input_filter "INPUT_FILTER" for further
 information on how filters are used. If the \c FILTER_PATTERNS tag is empty or if
 none of the patterns match the file name, \ref cfg_input_filter "INPUT_FILTER" is
 applied.
 <br>Note that for custom extensions or not directly supported extensions you also
 need to set \ref cfg_extension_mapping "EXTENSION_MAPPING" for the extension
 otherwise the files are not properly processed by Doxygen.<br>
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='FILTER_SOURCE_FILES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c FILTER_SOURCE_FILES tag is set to \c YES, the input filter (if set using
 \ref cfg_input_filter "INPUT_FILTER") will also be used to filter the input
 files that are used for producing the source files to browse
 (i.e. when \ref cfg_source_browser "SOURCE_BROWSER" is set to \c YES).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='FILTER_SOURCE_PATTERNS' format='string' depends='FILTER_SOURCE_FILES'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c FILTER_SOURCE_PATTERNS tag can be used to specify source filters per
 file pattern. A pattern will override the setting
 for \ref cfg_filter_patterns "FILTER_PATTERN" (if any)
 and it is also possible to disable source filtering for a specific pattern
 using `*.ext=` (so without naming a filter).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='USE_MDFILE_AS_MAINPAGE' format='string' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c USE_MDFILE_AS_MAINPAGE tag refers to the name of a markdown file that
 is part of the input, its contents will be placed on the main page (`index.html`).
 This can be useful if you have a project on for instance GitHub and want to reuse
 the introduction page also for the Doxygen output.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='FORTRAN_COMMENT_AFTER' defval='72' minval='7' maxval='10000'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The Fortran standard specifies that for fixed formatted Fortran code all characters
 from position 72 are to be considered as comment. A common extension is to allow
 longer lines before the automatic comment starts.
 The setting \c FORTRAN_COMMENT_AFTER will also make it possible that longer lines can be
 processed before the automatic comment starts.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Source_Browser' docs='Configuration options related to source browsing'>
    <option type='bool' id='SOURCE_BROWSER' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SOURCE_BROWSER tag is set to \c YES then a list of source files will
 be generated. Documented entities will be cross-referenced with these sources.
 <br>Note: To get rid of all source code in the generated output, make sure that also
 \ref cfg_verbatim_headers "VERBATIM_HEADERS" is set to \c NO.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INLINE_SOURCES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Setting the \c INLINE_SOURCES tag to \c YES will include the body
 of functions, multi-line macros, enums or list initialized
 variables directly into the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='STRIP_CODE_COMMENTS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Setting the \c STRIP_CODE_COMMENTS tag to \c YES will instruct
 Doxygen to hide any special comment blocks from generated source code
 fragments. Normal C, C++ and Fortran comments will always remain visible.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='REFERENCED_BY_RELATION' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c REFERENCED_BY_RELATION tag is set to \c YES
 then for each documented entity all documented
 functions referencing it will be listed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='REFERENCES_RELATION' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c REFERENCES_RELATION tag is set to \c YES
 then for each documented function all documented entities
 called/used by that function will be listed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='REFERENCES_LINK_SOURCE' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c REFERENCES_LINK_SOURCE tag is set to \c YES
 and \ref cfg_source_browser "SOURCE_BROWSER" tag is set to \c YES then the hyperlinks from
 functions in \ref cfg_references_relation "REFERENCES_RELATION" and
 \ref cfg_referenced_by_relation "REFERENCED_BY_RELATION" lists will
 link to the source code.  Otherwise they will link to the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SOURCE_TOOLTIPS' defval='1' depends='SOURCE_BROWSER'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
If \c SOURCE_TOOLTIPS is enabled (the default) then hovering a hyperlink in the
source code will show a tooltip with additional information such as prototype,
brief description and links to the definition and documentation. Since this will
make the HTML file larger and loading of large files a bit slower, you can opt
to disable this feature.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='USE_HTAGS' defval='0' depends='SOURCE_BROWSER'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c USE_HTAGS tag is set to \c YES then the references to source code
 will point to the HTML generated by the \c htags(1) tool instead of Doxygen
 built-in source browser. The \c htags tool is part of GNU's global source
 tagging system (see https://www.gnu.org/software/global/global.html). You
 will need version 4.8.6 or higher.
<br>
 To use it do the following:
 -# Install the latest version of \c global
 -# Enable \ref cfg_source_browser "SOURCE_BROWSER" and \c USE_HTAGS in the configuration file
 -# Make sure the \ref cfg_input "INPUT" points to the root of the source tree
 -# Run \c doxygen as normal
<br>
 Doxygen will invoke \c htags (and that will in turn invoke \c gtags), so these tools
 must be available from the command line (i.e. in the search path).
<br>
 The result: instead of the source browser generated by Doxygen, the links to
 source code will now point to the output of \c htags.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>

    <option type='bool' id='VERBATIM_HEADERS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  If the \c VERBATIM_HEADERS tag is set the \c YES then Doxygen
  will generate a verbatim copy of the header file for each class for
  which an include is specified. Set to \c NO to disable this.
  \sa Section \ref cmdclass "\\class".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='CLANG_ASSISTED_PARSING' setting='USE_LIBCLANG' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  If the \c CLANG_ASSISTED_PARSING tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will use the
  <a href="http://clang.llvm.org/">clang parser</a> for more accurate parsing
  at the cost of reduced performance. This can be particularly helpful with
  template rich C++ code for which Doxygen's built-in parser lacks the
  necessary type information.

  @note The availability of this option depends on whether or not Doxygen
  was generated with the `-Duse_libclang=ON` option for CMake.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='CLANG_ADD_INC_PATHS' setting='USE_LIBCLANG' depends='CLANG_ASSISTED_PARSING' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  If the \c CLANG_ASSISTED_PARSING tag is set to \c YES and the \c CLANG_ADD_INC_PATHS
  tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will add the directory of each input to the
  include path.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='CLANG_OPTIONS' format='string' setting='USE_LIBCLANG' depends='CLANG_ASSISTED_PARSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If clang assisted parsing is enabled you can provide the compiler with command
 line options that you would normally use when invoking the compiler. Note that
 the include paths will already be set by Doxygen for the files and directories
 specified with \ref cfg_input "INPUT" and \ref cfg_include_path "INCLUDE_PATH".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='CLANG_DATABASE_PATH' setting='USE_LIBCLANG' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If clang assisted parsing is enabled you can provide the clang parser with the
 path to the directory containing a file called `compile_commands.json`.
 This file is the <a href="http://clang.llvm.org/docs/HowToSetupToolingForLLVM.html">
 compilation database</a> containing the options used when the source files were built.
 This is equivalent to specifying the `-p` option to a clang tool, such as `clang-check`.
 These options will then be passed to the parser. Any options specified with
 \ref cfg_clang_options "CLANG_OPTIONS" will be added as well.

 @note The availability of this option depends on whether or not Doxygen
 was generated with the `-Duse_libclang=ON` option for CMake.
 ]]>
        </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Index' docs='Configuration options related to the alphabetical class index'>
    <option type='bool' id='ALPHABETICAL_INDEX' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c ALPHABETICAL_INDEX tag is set to \c YES, an alphabetical index
 of all compounds will be generated. Enable this if the project contains
 a lot of classes, structs, unions or interfaces.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='IGNORE_PREFIX' format='string' depends='ALPHABETICAL_INDEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c IGNORE_PREFIX tag can be used to specify a prefix 
 (or a list of prefixes) that should be ignored while generating the index headers.
 The \c IGNORE_PREFIX tag works for classes, function and member names.
 The entity will be placed in the alphabetical list under the first letter of the entity name that remains
 after removing the prefix.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='HTML' docs='Configuration options related to the HTML output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_HTML' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_HTML tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 generate HTML output
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='HTML_OUTPUT' format='dir' defval='html' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_OUTPUT tag is used to specify where the HTML docs will be put.
 If a relative path is entered the value of \ref cfg_output_directory "OUTPUT_DIRECTORY" will be
 put in front of it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='HTML_FILE_EXTENSION' format='string' defval='.html' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_FILE_EXTENSION tag can be used to specify the file extension for
 each generated HTML page (for example: <code>.htm, .php, .asp</code>).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='HTML_HEADER' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_HEADER tag can be used to specify a user-defined HTML
 header file for each generated HTML page.
 If the tag is left blank Doxygen will generate a
 standard header.
<br>
 To get valid HTML the header file that
 includes any scripts and style sheets that Doxygen
 needs, which is dependent on the configuration options used (e.g. the
 setting \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW").
 It is highly recommended to start with a default header using
\verbatim
doxygen -w html new_header.html new_footer.html new_stylesheet.css YourConfigFile
\endverbatim
 and then modify the file \c new_header.html.

 See also section \ref doxygen_usage for information on how to generate
 the default header that Doxygen normally uses.

 @note The header is subject to change so you typically
 have to regenerate the default header when upgrading to a newer version of
 Doxygen.
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxywizard='0' doxyfile='0'>
<![CDATA[
 The following markers have a special meaning inside the header and footer:
 <dl>
 <dt><code>$title</code><dd>will be replaced with the title of the page.
 <dt><code>$datetime</code><dd>will be replaced with the current date and time.
 <dt><code>$date</code><dd>will be replaced with the current date.
 <dt><code>$time</code><dd>will be replaced with the current time.
 <dt><code>$year</code><dd>will be replaces with the current year.
 <dt><code>$showdate(<format>)</code><dd>will be replaced with the current date
           and time according to the format as specified by `<format>`. The
           `<format>` follows the rules as specified for the
           \ref cmdshowdate "\\showdate" command with the exception that no `)`
           is allowed in the `<format>`.
 <dt><code>$doxygenversion</code><dd>will be replaced with the version of Doxygen
 <dt><code>$projectname</code><dd>will be replaced with the name of
            the project (see \ref cfg_project_name "PROJECT_NAME")
 <dt><code>$projectnumber</code><dd>will be replaced with the project number
            (see \ref cfg_project_number "PROJECT_NUMBER")
 <dt><code>$projectbrief</code><dd>will be replaced with the project brief
            description (see \ref cfg_project_brief "PROJECT_BRIEF")
 <dt><code>$projectlogo</code><dd>will be replaced with the project logo
            (see \ref cfg_project_logo "PROJECT_LOGO")
 <dt><code>$generatedby</code><dd>will be replaced with the output language dependent
            version of the text "Generated by" or when the
            \ref cfg_timestamp "TIMESTAMP" is set by the output language
            dependent version of the text &quot;Generated on `$datetime` for `$projectname` by&quot;.
 <dt><code>$stylesheet</code><dd>will be replaced with the setting of
            \ref cfg_html_stylesheet "HTML_STYLESHEET" unless it is empty or the file in which case
            it is replaced by the default setting `doxygen.css`.
 <dt><code>$extrastylesheet</code><dd>will be replaced with the setting of
            \ref cfg_html_extra_stylesheet "HTML_EXTRA_STYLESHEET" including the required
            HTML tags for each extra stylesheet.
 <dt><code>$treeview</code><dd>will be replaced with links to
            the JavaScript and style sheets needed for the navigation tree
            (or an empty string when \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW"
            is disabled).
 <dt><code>$search</code><dd>will be replaced with a links to
            the JavaScript and style sheets needed for the search engine
            (or an empty string when \ref cfg_searchengine "SEARCHENGINE"
            is disabled).
 <dt><code>$searchbox</code><dd>will be replaced with the HTML code needed for
            the search box to be shown
            (or an empty string when \ref cfg_searchengine "SEARCHENGINE"
            is disabled).
 <dt><code>$mathjax</code><dd>will be replaced with a links to
            the JavaScript and style sheets needed for the MathJax feature
            (or an empty string when \ref cfg_use_mathjax "USE_MATHJAX" is disabled).
 <dt><code>$relpath^</code><dd>
            If \ref cfg_create_subdirs "CREATE_SUBDIRS" is enabled, the command <code>$relpath^</code> can be
            used to produce a relative path to the root of the HTML output directory,
            e.g. use <code>$relpath^doxygen.css</code>, to refer to the standard style sheet.
 <dt><code>$navpath</code><dd>will be replaced with a path as required by
            \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW"
 </dl>

 To cope with differences in the layout of the header and footer that depend on
 configuration settings, the header can also contain special blocks that
 will be copied to the output or skipped depending on the configuration.
 Such blocks have the following form:
\verbatim
 <!--BEGIN BLOCKNAME-->
 Some context copied when condition BLOCKNAME holds
 <!--END BLOCKNAME-->
 <!--BEGIN !BLOCKNAME-->
 Some context copied when condition BLOCKNAME does not hold
 <!--END !BLOCKNAME-->
\endverbatim
 The following block names are supported:
 <dl>
 <dt><code>DISABLE_INDEX</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_disable_index "DISABLE_INDEX" option is enabled (so when the index is disabled).
 <dt><code>GENERATE_TREEVIEW</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW" option is enabled.
 <dt><code>SEARCHENGINE</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_searchengine "SEARCHENGINE" option is enabled.
 <dt><code>PROJECT_NAME</code><dd>Content within the block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_project_name "PROJECT_NAME" option is not empty.
 <dt><code>PROJECT_NUMBER</code><dd>Content within the block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_project_number "PROJECT_NUMBER" option is not empty.
 <dt><code>PROJECT_BRIEF</code><dd>Content within the block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_project_brief "PROJECT_BRIEF" option is not empty.
 <dt><code>PROJECT_LOGO</code><dd>Content within the block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_project_logo "PROJECT_LOGO" option is not empty.
 <dt><code>FULL_SIDEBAR</code><dd>Content within the block is copied to the output
     if the \ref cfg_full_sidebar "FULL_SIDEBAR",
     \ref cfg_disable_index "DISABLE_INDEX" and \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW"
     options are all enabled.
 <dt><code>TITLEAREA</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     if a title is visible at the top of each page. This is the case
     if either \ref cfg_project_name "PROJECT_NAME",
     \ref cfg_project_brief "PROJECT_BRIEF", \ref cfg_project_logo "PROJECT_LOGO"
     is filled in or if both \ref cfg_disable_index "DISABLE_INDEX" and
     \ref cfg_searchengine "SEARCHENGINE" are enabled.
 </dl>
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs documentation='0'>
<![CDATA[
 For a description of the possible markers and block names see the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>

    <option type='string' id='HTML_FOOTER' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_FOOTER tag can be used to specify a user-defined HTML footer for
 each generated HTML page.
 If the tag is left blank Doxygen will generate a standard footer.

 See \ref cfg_html_header "HTML_HEADER" for more information on
 how to generate a default footer and what special commands can be
 used inside the footer.

 See also section \ref doxygen_usage for information on how to generate
 the default footer that Doxygen normally uses.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='HTML_STYLESHEET' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_STYLESHEET tag can be used to specify a user-defined cascading
 style sheet that is used by each HTML page. It can be used to
 fine-tune the look of the HTML output. If left blank Doxygen
 will generate a default style sheet.

 See also section \ref doxygen_usage for information on how to generate
 the style sheet that Doxygen normally uses.

 \note It is recommended to use
 \ref cfg_html_extra_stylesheet "HTML_EXTRA_STYLESHEET" instead of this tag,
 as it is more robust and
 this tag (<code>HTML_STYLESHEET</code>) will in the future become obsolete.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='HTML_EXTRA_STYLESHEET' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_EXTRA_STYLESHEET tag can be used to specify additional
 user-defined cascading style sheets that are included after the standard
 style sheets created by Doxygen. Using this option one can overrule
 certain style aspects. This is preferred over using \ref cfg_html_stylesheet "HTML_STYLESHEET"
 since it does not replace the standard style sheet and is therefore more
 robust against future updates. Doxygen will copy the style sheet files to
 the output directory.
 \note The order of the extra style sheet files is of importance (e.g. the last
 style sheet in the list overrules the setting of the previous ones in the list).
 \note Since the styling of scrollbars can currently not be overruled in Webkit/Chromium, the
 styling will be left out of the default doxygen.css if one or more extra stylesheets
 have been specified.
 So if scrollbar customization is desired it has to be added explicitly.
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxywizard='0' doxyfile='0'>
<![CDATA[
 Here is an example style sheet that gives the contents area a fixed width:
\verbatim
body {
        background-color: #CCC;
        color: black;
        margin: 0;
}

div.contents {
        margin-bottom: 10px;
        padding: 12px;
        margin-left: auto;
        margin-right: auto;
        width: 960px;
        background-color: white;
        border-radius: 8px;
}

#titlearea {
        background-color: white;
}

hr.footer {
        display: none;
}

.footer {
        background-color: #AAA;
}
\endverbatim
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs documentation='0'>
<![CDATA[
 For an example see the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='HTML_EXTRA_FILES' format='file' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_EXTRA_FILES tag can be used to specify one or more extra images or
 other source files which should be copied to the HTML output directory. Note
 that these files will be copied to the base HTML output directory. Use the
 <code>$relpath^</code> marker in the \ref cfg_html_header "HTML_HEADER" and/or
 \ref cfg_html_footer "HTML_FOOTER" files to load these
 files. In the \ref cfg_html_stylesheet "HTML_STYLESHEET" file, use the file name only. Also note that
 the files will be copied as-is; there are no commands or markers available.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='HTML_COLORSTYLE' defval='AUTO_LIGHT' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_COLORSTYLE tag can be used to specify if the generated HTML output should be rendered with
 a dark or light theme.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="LIGHT" desc="always generates light mode output"/>
      <value name="DARK" desc="always generates dark mode output"/>
      <value name="AUTO_LIGHT" desc="automatically sets the mode according to the user preference, uses light mode if no preference is set (the default)"/>
      <value name="AUTO_DARK" desc="automatically sets the mode according to the user preference, uses dark mode if no preference is set"/>
      <value name="TOGGLE" desc="allows a user to switch between light and dark mode via a button"/>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='HTML_COLORSTYLE_HUE' minval='0' maxval='359' defval='220' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_COLORSTYLE_HUE tag controls the color of the HTML output.
 Doxygen will adjust the colors in the style sheet and background images
 according to this color. Hue is specified as an angle on a color-wheel,
 see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hue for more information.
 For instance the value 0 represents red, 60 is yellow, 120 is green,
 180 is cyan, 240 is blue, 300 purple, and 360 is red again.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='HTML_COLORSTYLE_SAT' minval='0' maxval='255' defval='100' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_COLORSTYLE_SAT tag controls the purity (or saturation) of
 the colors in the HTML output. For a value of 0 the output will use
 gray-scales only. A value of 255 will produce the most vivid colors.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='HTML_COLORSTYLE_GAMMA' minval='40' maxval='240' defval='80' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c HTML_COLORSTYLE_GAMMA tag controls the gamma correction applied to
 the luminance component of the colors in the HTML output. Values below
 100 gradually make the output lighter, whereas values above 100 make
 the output darker. The value divided by 100 is the actual gamma applied,
 so 80 represents a gamma of 0.8, The value 220 represents a gamma of 2.2,
 and 100 does not change the gamma.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HTML_DYNAMIC_MENUS' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HTML_DYNAMIC_MENUS tag is set to \c YES then the generated HTML
 documentation will contain a main index with vertical navigation menus that
 are dynamically created via JavaScript. If disabled, the navigation index will consists of
 multiple levels of tabs that are statically embedded in every HTML page.
 Disable this option to support browsers that do not have JavaScript, like
 the Qt help browser.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HTML_DYNAMIC_SECTIONS' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HTML_DYNAMIC_SECTIONS tag is set to \c YES then the generated HTML
 documentation will contain sections that can be hidden and shown after the
 page has loaded.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HTML_CODE_FOLDING' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HTML_CODE_FOLDING tag is set to \c YES then classes and functions can
 be dynamically folded and expanded in the generated HTML source code.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HTML_COPY_CLIPBOARD' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HTML_COPY_CLIPBOARD tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will show an
 icon in the top right corner of code and text fragments that allows the user
 to copy its content to the clipboard.
 Note this only works if supported by the browser and the web page is served via a
 <a href="https://www.w3.org/TR/secure-contexts/">secure context</a>, i.e. using the
 https: or file: protocol.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='HTML_PROJECT_COOKIE' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Doxygen stores a couple of settings persistently in the browser (via e.g. cookies).
 By default these settings apply to all HTML pages generated by Doxygen across all projects.
 The \c HTML_PROJECT_COOKIE tag can be used to store the settings under a project specific
 key, such that the user preferences will be stored separately.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='HTML_INDEX_NUM_ENTRIES' minval='0' maxval='9999' defval='100' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 With \c HTML_INDEX_NUM_ENTRIES one can control the preferred number of
 entries shown in the various tree structured indices initially; the user
 can expand and collapse entries dynamically later on. Doxygen will expand
 the tree to such a level that at most the specified number of entries are
 visible (unless a fully collapsed tree already exceeds this amount).
 So setting the number of entries 1 will produce a full collapsed tree by
 default. 0 is a special value representing an infinite number of entries
 and will result in a full expanded tree by default.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_DOCSET' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_DOCSET tag is set to \c YES, additional index files
 will be generated that can be used as input for
 <a href="https://developer.apple.com/xcode/">Apple's Xcode 3
 integrated development environment</a>, introduced with OSX 10.5 (Leopard).
 To create a documentation set, Doxygen will generate a Makefile in the
 HTML output directory. Running \c make will produce the docset in that
 directory and running <code>make install</code> will install the docset in
 <code>~/Library/Developer/Shared/Documentation/DocSets</code>
 so that Xcode will find it at startup. See
 https://developer.apple.com/library/archive/featuredarticles/DoxygenXcode/_index.html
 for more information.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOCSET_FEEDNAME' format='string' defval='Doxygen generated docs' depends='GENERATE_DOCSET'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag determines the name of the docset
 feed. A documentation feed provides an umbrella under which multiple
 documentation sets from a single provider (such as a company or product suite)
 can be grouped.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOCSET_FEEDURL' format='string' depends='GENERATE_DOCSET'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag determines the URL of the docset
 feed. A documentation feed provides an umbrella under which multiple
 documentation sets from a single provider (such as a company or product suite)
 can be grouped.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOCSET_BUNDLE_ID' format='string' defval='org.doxygen.Project' depends='GENERATE_DOCSET'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 This tag specifies a string that
 should uniquely identify the documentation set bundle. This should be a
 reverse domain-name style string, e.g. <code>com.mycompany.MyDocSet</code>.
 Doxygen will append <code>.docset</code> to the name.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOCSET_PUBLISHER_ID' format='string' defval='org.doxygen.Publisher' depends='GENERATE_DOCSET'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
The \c DOCSET_PUBLISHER_ID
tag specifies a string that should uniquely identify
the documentation publisher. This should be a reverse domain-name style
string, e.g. <code>com.mycompany.MyDocSet.documentation</code>.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOCSET_PUBLISHER_NAME' format='string' defval='Publisher' depends='GENERATE_DOCSET'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
The \c DOCSET_PUBLISHER_NAME tag identifies the documentation publisher.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_HTMLHELP' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_HTMLHELP tag is set to \c YES then
 Doxygen generates three additional HTML index files:
 \c index.hhp, \c index.hhc, and \c index.hhk. The \c index.hhp is a
 project file that can be read by Microsoft's HTML Help Workshop
 on Windows.
  In the beginning of 2021 Microsoft took the original page, with a.o. the download links,
  offline (the HTML help workshop was already many years in maintenance mode).
  You can download the HTML help workshop from the web archives at
  <a href="http://web.archive.org/web/20160201063255/http://download.microsoft.com/download/0/A/9/0A939EF6-E31C-430F-A3DF-DFAE7960D564/htmlhelp.exe">Installation executable</a>.
<br>
 The HTML Help Workshop contains a compiler that can convert all HTML output
 generated by Doxygen into a single compiled HTML file (`.chm`). Compiled
 HTML files are now used as the Windows 98 help format, and will replace
 the old Windows help format (`.hlp`) on all Windows platforms in the future.
 Compressed HTML files also contain an index, a table of contents,
 and you can search for words in the documentation.
 The HTML workshop also contains a viewer for compressed HTML files.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='CHM_FILE' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTMLHELP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  The \c CHM_FILE tag can
  be used to specify the file name of the resulting `.chm` file. You
  can add a path in front of the file if the result should not be
  written to the html output directory.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='HHC_LOCATION' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTMLHELP' abspath='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  The \c HHC_LOCATION tag can
  be used to specify the location (absolute path including file name) of
  the HTML help compiler (\c hhc.exe). If non-empty, Doxygen will try to run
  the HTML help compiler on the generated \c index.hhp.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_CHI' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTMLHELP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c GENERATE_CHI flag
 controls if a separate `.chi` index file is generated (\c YES) or that
 it should be included in the main `.chm` file (\c NO).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='CHM_INDEX_ENCODING' format='string' defval='' depends='GENERATE_HTMLHELP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c CHM_INDEX_ENCODING
 is used to encode HtmlHelp index (\c hhk), content (\c hhc) and project file
 content.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='BINARY_TOC' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTMLHELP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c BINARY_TOC flag
 controls whether a binary table of contents is generated (\c YES) or a
 normal table of contents (\c NO) in the `.chm` file. Furthermore it enables
 the `Previous` and `Next` buttons.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='TOC_EXPAND' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTMLHELP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c TOC_EXPAND flag can be set to \c YES to add extra items for
 group members to the table of contents of the HTML help documentation
 and to the tree view.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='SITEMAP_URL' format='string' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c SITEMAP_URL tag is used to specify the full URL of the place where the
 generated documentation will be placed on the server by the user during the deployment
 of the documentation.
 The generated sitemap is called `sitemap.xml` and placed on the directory specified by
 \ref cfg_html_output "HTML_OUTPUT". In case no \c SITEMAP_URL is specified no 
 sitemap is generated.
 For information about the sitemap protocol see https://www.sitemaps.org
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_QHP' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_QHP tag is set to \c YES and both \ref cfg_qhp_namespace "QHP_NAMESPACE"
 and \ref cfg_qhp_virtual_folder "QHP_VIRTUAL_FOLDER" are set, an additional index file will
 be generated that can be used as input for Qt's qhelpgenerator
 to generate a Qt Compressed Help (`.qch`) of the generated HTML
 documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='QCH_FILE' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_QHP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \ref cfg_qhg_location "QHG_LOCATION" tag is specified, the \c QCH_FILE tag can
 be used to specify the file name of the resulting `.qch` file.
 The path specified is relative to the HTML output folder.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='QHP_NAMESPACE' format='string' defval='org.doxygen.Project' depends='GENERATE_QHP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c QHP_NAMESPACE tag specifies the namespace to use when generating
 Qt Help Project output. For more information please see
 <a href="https://doc.qt.io/archives/qt-4.8/qthelpproject.html#namespace">Qt Help Project / Namespace</a>.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='QHP_VIRTUAL_FOLDER' format='string' defval='doc' depends='GENERATE_QHP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c QHP_VIRTUAL_FOLDER tag specifies the namespace to use when
 generating Qt Help Project output. For more information please see
 <a href="https://doc.qt.io/archives/qt-4.8/qthelpproject.html#virtual-folders">Qt Help Project / Virtual Folders</a>.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='QHP_CUST_FILTER_NAME' format='string' defval='' depends='GENERATE_QHP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  If the \c QHP_CUST_FILTER_NAME tag is set, it specifies the name of a custom filter to add. For more information please see
  <a href="https://doc.qt.io/archives/qt-4.8/qthelpproject.html#custom-filters">Qt Help Project / Custom Filters</a>.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='QHP_CUST_FILTER_ATTRS' format='string' defval='' depends='GENERATE_QHP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  The \c QHP_CUST_FILTER_ATTRS tag specifies the list of the attributes of the custom filter to add.
  For more information please see
  <a href="https://doc.qt.io/archives/qt-4.8/qthelpproject.html#custom-filters">Qt Help Project / Custom Filters</a>.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='QHP_SECT_FILTER_ATTRS' format='string' defval='' depends='GENERATE_QHP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  The \c QHP_SECT_FILTER_ATTRS tag specifies the list of the attributes this project's filter section matches.
  <a href="https://doc.qt.io/archives/qt-4.8/qthelpproject.html#filter-attributes">Qt Help Project / Filter Attributes</a>.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='QHG_LOCATION' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_QHP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c QHG_LOCATION tag can
 be used to specify the location (absolute path including file name) of
 Qt's qhelpgenerator.
 If non-empty Doxygen will try to run qhelpgenerator on the generated `.qhp` file.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_ECLIPSEHELP' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_ECLIPSEHELP tag is set to \c YES, additional index files
 will be generated, together with the HTML files, they form an `Eclipse` help
 plugin.

 To install this plugin and make it available under the help contents
 menu in `Eclipse`, the contents of the directory containing the HTML and XML
 files needs to be copied into the plugins directory of eclipse. The name of
 the directory within the plugins directory should be the same as
 the \ref cfg_eclipse_doc_id "ECLIPSE_DOC_ID" value.

 After copying `Eclipse` needs to be restarted before the help appears.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='ECLIPSE_DOC_ID' format='string' defval='org.doxygen.Project' depends='GENERATE_ECLIPSEHELP'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 A unique identifier for the `Eclipse` help plugin. When installing the plugin
 the directory name containing the HTML and XML files should also have
 this name. Each documentation set should have its own identifier.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='DISABLE_INDEX' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If you want full control over the layout of the generated HTML pages it
 might be necessary to disable the index and replace it with your own.
 The \c DISABLE_INDEX tag can be used to turn on/off the condensed index (tabs) at
 top of each HTML page. A value of \c NO enables the index and the
 value \c YES disables it. Since the tabs in the index contain the same
 information as the navigation tree, you can set this option to \c YES if
 you also set \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW" to \c YES.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_TREEVIEW' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c GENERATE_TREEVIEW tag is used to specify whether a tree-like index
 structure should be generated to display hierarchical information.
 If the tag value is set to \c YES, a side panel will be generated
 containing a tree-like index structure (just like the one that
 is generated for HTML Help). For this to work a browser that supports
 JavaScript, DHTML, CSS and frames is required (i.e. any modern browser).
 Windows users are probably better off using the HTML help feature.

 Via custom style sheets (see \ref cfg_html_extra_stylesheet "HTML_EXTRA_STYLESHEET")
 one can further fine tune the look of the index (see \ref doxygen_finetune).
 As an example, the default style sheet generated by Doxygen has an
 example that shows how to put an image at the root of the tree instead of
 the \ref cfg_project_name "PROJECT_NAME".

 Since the tree basically has the same information as the tab index, you could
 consider setting \ref cfg_disable_index "DISABLE_INDEX" to \c YES when
 enabling this option.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='FULL_SIDEBAR' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
  When both \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW" and \ref cfg_disable_index "DISABLE_INDEX"
  are set to \c YES, then the
  \c FULL_SIDEBAR option determines if the side bar is limited to only the
  treeview area (value \c NO) or if it should extend to the full height of the
  window (value \c YES). Setting this to \c YES gives a layout similar to
  https://docs.readthedocs.io with more room for contents,
  but less room for the project logo, title, and description.

  If either \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW" or \ref cfg_disable_index "DISABLE_INDEX"
  is set to \c NO, this option
  has no effect.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='ENUM_VALUES_PER_LINE' minval='0' maxval='20' defval='4' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c ENUM_VALUES_PER_LINE tag can be used to set the number of enum values
 that Doxygen will group on one line in the generated HTML documentation.
 <br>Note that a value of 0 will completely suppress the enum values from
 appearing in the overview section.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SHOW_ENUM_VALUES' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When the \c SHOW_ENUM_VALUES tag is set doxygen will show the specified enumeration values
 besides the enumeration mnemonics.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='TREEVIEW_WIDTH' minval='0' maxval='1500' defval='250' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the treeview is enabled (see \ref cfg_generate_treeview "GENERATE_TREEVIEW") then this tag can be
 used to set the initial width (in pixels) of the frame in which the tree
 is shown.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXT_LINKS_IN_WINDOW' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXT_LINKS_IN_WINDOW option is set to \c YES, Doxygen will open
 links to external symbols imported via tag files in a separate window.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='OBFUSCATE_EMAILS' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
If the \c OBFUSCATE_EMAILS tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
obfuscate email addresses.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='HTML_FORMULA_FORMAT' defval='png' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c HTML_FORMULA_FORMAT option is set to \c svg, Doxygen will use the pdf2svg
 tool (see https://github.com/dawbarton/pdf2svg) or inkscape (see https://inkscape.org)
 to generate formulas as SVG images instead of
 PNGs for the HTML output. These images will generally look nicer at scaled resolutions.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="png" desc="(the default)"/>
      <value name="svg" desc="(looks nicer but requires the pdf2svg or inkscape tool)"/>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='FORMULA_FONTSIZE' minval='8' maxval='50' defval='10' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Use this tag to change the font size of \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ formulas included
 as images in the HTML documentation.
 When you change the font size after a successful Doxygen run you need
 to manually remove any `form_*.png` images from the HTML
 output directory to force them to be regenerated.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='FORMULA_MACROFILE' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c FORMULA_MACROFILE can contain \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ `\newcommand` and
 `\renewcommand` commands to create new \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ commands to be used
 in formulas as building blocks.
 See the section \ref formulas for details.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='USE_MATHJAX' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Enable the \c USE_MATHJAX option to render \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ formulas using MathJax
 (see https://www.mathjax.org) which uses client side JavaScript for the
 rendering instead of using pre-rendered bitmaps. Use this if you do not
 have \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ installed or if you want to formulas look prettier in the HTML
 output. When enabled you may also need to install MathJax separately and
 configure the path to it using the \ref cfg_mathjax_relpath "MATHJAX_RELPATH"
 option.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='MATHJAX_VERSION' defval='MathJax_2' depends='USE_MATHJAX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 With \c MATHJAX_VERSION it is possible to specify the MathJax version to be used.
 Note that the different versions of MathJax have different requirements with regards to
 the different settings, so it is possible that also other MathJax settings have to be changed
 when switching between the different MathJax versions.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="MathJax_2"/>
      <value name="MathJax_3"/>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='MATHJAX_FORMAT' defval='HTML-CSS' depends='USE_MATHJAX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When MathJax is enabled you can set the default output format to be used for
 the MathJax output.
 For more details about the output format see <a href="http://docs.mathjax.org/en/v2.7-latest/output.html">MathJax version 2</a>
 and <a href="http://docs.mathjax.org/en/latest/web/components/output.html">MathJax version 3</a>.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="HTML-CSS" desc="(which is slower, but has the best compatibility. This is the name for Mathjax version 2, for MathJax version 3 this will be translated into \c chtml)"/>
      <value name="NativeMML" desc="(i.e. MathML. Only supported for MathJax 2. For MathJax version 3 \c chtml will be used instead.)"/>
      <value name="chtml" desc="(This is the name for Mathjax version 3, for MathJax version 2 this will be translated into \c HTML-CSS)"/>
      <value name="SVG"/>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='MATHJAX_RELPATH' format='string' depends='USE_MATHJAX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When MathJax is enabled you need to specify the location relative to the
 HTML output directory using the \c MATHJAX_RELPATH option. The destination
 directory should contain the `MathJax.js` script. For instance, if the \c mathjax
 directory is located at the same level as the HTML output directory, then
 \c MATHJAX_RELPATH should be <code>../mathjax</code>. The default value points to
 the MathJax Content Delivery Network so you can quickly see the result without
 installing MathJax.  However, it is strongly recommended to install a local
 copy of MathJax from https://www.mathjax.org before deployment.

 The default value is:
 - in case of  MathJax version 2: https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/mathjax@2
 - in case of  MathJax version 3: https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/mathjax@3
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='MATHJAX_EXTENSIONS' format='string' depends='USE_MATHJAX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MATHJAX_EXTENSIONS tag can be used to specify one or more MathJax extension
 names that should be enabled during MathJax rendering. For example for MathJax version 2
 (see https://docs.mathjax.org/en/v2.7-latest/tex.html#tex-and-latex-extensions):
\verbatim
MATHJAX_EXTENSIONS     = TeX/AMSmath TeX/AMSsymbols
\endverbatim
For example for MathJax version 3 (see http://docs.mathjax.org/en/latest/input/tex/extensions/index.html):
\verbatim
MATHJAX_EXTENSIONS     = ams
\endverbatim
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='MATHJAX_CODEFILE' format='string' depends='USE_MATHJAX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MATHJAX_CODEFILE tag can be used to specify a file with JavaScript
 pieces of code that will be used on startup of the MathJax code.
 See
<a href="http://docs.mathjax.org/en/v2.7-latest/output.html">the MathJax site</a>
 for more details.
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxywizard='0' doxyfile='0'>
<![CDATA[
 As an example to disable the "Math Renderer" menu item in the "Math
 Settings" menu of MathJax:
\verbatim
MATHJAX_CODEFILE = disableRenderer.js
\endverbatim
  with in the file <code>disableRenderer.js</code>:
\verbatim
  MathJax.Hub.Config({
   menuSettings: {
    showRenderer: false,
   }
  });
\endverbatim
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs documentation='0'>
<![CDATA[
 For an example see the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SEARCHENGINE' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_HTML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When the \c SEARCHENGINE tag is enabled Doxygen will generate a search box
 for the HTML output. The underlying search engine uses JavaScript
 and DHTML and should work on any modern browser. Note that when using
 HTML help (\ref cfg_generate_htmlhelp "GENERATE_HTMLHELP"),
 Qt help (\ref cfg_generate_qhp "GENERATE_QHP"), or docsets
 (\ref cfg_generate_docset "GENERATE_DOCSET") there is already a search
 function so this one should typically be disabled. For large projects
 the JavaScript based search engine can be slow, then enabling
 \ref cfg_server_based_search "SERVER_BASED_SEARCH" may provide a
 better solution.

 It is possible to search using the keyboard;
 to jump to the search box use <code>\<access key\> + S</code> (what the <code>\<access key\></code> is
 depends on the OS and browser, but it is typically <code>\<CTRL\></code>, <code>\<ALT\></code>/<code>\<option\></code>, or both).
 Inside the search box use the <code>\<cursor down key\></code> to jump into the search
 results window, the results can be navigated using the <code>\<cursor keys\></code>.
 Press <code>\<Enter\></code> to select an item or <code>\<escape\></code> to cancel the search. The
 filter options can be selected when the cursor is inside the search box
 by pressing <code>\<Shift\>+\<cursor down\></code>. Also here use the <code>\<cursor keys\></code> to
 select a filter and <code>\<Enter\></code> or <code>\<escape\></code> to activate or cancel the filter option.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SERVER_BASED_SEARCH' defval='0' depends='SEARCHENGINE'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
When the \c SERVER_BASED_SEARCH tag is enabled the search engine will be
implemented using a web server instead of a web client using JavaScript.

There are two flavors of web server based searching depending on the
\ref cfg_external_search "EXTERNAL_SEARCH" setting. When disabled,
Doxygen will generate a PHP script for searching and an index file used
by the script. When \ref cfg_external_search "EXTERNAL_SEARCH" is
enabled the indexing and searching needs to be provided by external tools.
See the section \ref extsearch for details.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTERNAL_SEARCH' defval='0' depends='SEARCHENGINE'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When \c EXTERNAL_SEARCH tag is enabled Doxygen will no longer generate the PHP
 script for searching. Instead the search results are written to an XML file
 which needs to be processed by an external indexer. Doxygen will invoke an
 external search engine pointed to by the
 \ref cfg_searchengine_url "SEARCHENGINE_URL" option to obtain
 the search results.
 <br>Doxygen ships with an example indexer (\c doxyindexer) and
 search engine (<code>doxysearch.cgi</code>) which are based on the open source search
 engine library <a href="https://xapian.org/">Xapian</a>.
 <br>See the section \ref extsearch for details.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='SEARCHENGINE_URL' format='string' defval='' depends='SEARCHENGINE'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c SEARCHENGINE_URL should point to a search engine hosted by a web server
 which will return the search results when \ref cfg_external_search "EXTERNAL_SEARCH"
 is enabled.
 <br>Doxygen ships with an example indexer (\c doxyindexer) and
 search engine (<code>doxysearch.cgi</code>) which are based on the open source search
 engine library <a href="https://xapian.org/">Xapian</a>.
 See the section \ref extsearch for details.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='SEARCHDATA_FILE' format='file' defval='searchdata.xml' depends='SEARCHENGINE'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
When \ref cfg_server_based_search "SERVER_BASED_SEARCH" and
\ref cfg_external_search "EXTERNAL_SEARCH" are both enabled the unindexed
search data is written to a file for indexing by an external tool. With the
\c SEARCHDATA_FILE tag the name of this file can be specified.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='EXTERNAL_SEARCH_ID' format='string' defval='' depends='SEARCHENGINE'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
When \ref cfg_server_based_search "SERVER_BASED_SEARCH" and
\ref cfg_external_search "EXTERNAL_SEARCH" are both enabled the
\c EXTERNAL_SEARCH_ID tag can be used as an identifier for the project. This is
useful in combination with \ref cfg_extra_search_mappings "EXTRA_SEARCH_MAPPINGS"
to search through multiple projects and redirect the results back to the right project.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXTRA_SEARCH_MAPPINGS' format='string' depends='SEARCHENGINE'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c EXTRA_SEARCH_MAPPINGS tag can be used to enable searching through Doxygen
 projects other than the one defined by this configuration file, but that are
 all added to the same external search index. Each project needs to have a
 unique id set via \ref cfg_external_search_id "EXTERNAL_SEARCH_ID".
 The search mapping then maps the id of to a relative location where the
 documentation can be found.

 The format is:
\verbatim
EXTRA_SEARCH_MAPPINGS = tagname1=loc1 tagname2=loc2 ...
\endverbatim
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='LaTeX' docs='Configuration options related to the LaTeX output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_LATEX' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_LATEX tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 generate \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ output.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LATEX_OUTPUT' format='dir' defval='latex' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_OUTPUT tag is used to specify where the \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$
 docs will be put.
 If a relative path is entered the value of \ref cfg_output_directory "OUTPUT_DIRECTORY" will be
 put in front of it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LATEX_CMD_NAME' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_CMD_NAME tag can be used to specify the \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ command name to be invoked.
 <br>Note that when  not enabling \ref cfg_use_pdflatex "USE_PDFLATEX" the default is \c latex when
 enabling \ref cfg_use_pdflatex "USE_PDFLATEX" the default is \c pdflatex and when in the later case
 \c latex is chosen this is overwritten by \c pdflatex. For specific output languages the default can
 have been set differently, this depends on the implementation of the output language.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='MAKEINDEX_CMD_NAME' format='file' defval='makeindex' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MAKEINDEX_CMD_NAME tag can be used to specify the command name to
 generate index for \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$.

 @note This tag is used in the `Makefile` / `make.bat`.
 \sa  \ref cfg_latex_makeindex_cmd "LATEX_MAKEINDEX_CMD" for the part in the generated output file (`.tex`).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LATEX_MAKEINDEX_CMD' defval='makeindex' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_MAKEINDEX_CMD tag can be used to specify the command name to
 generate index for \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$. In case there is no backslash (`\`) as first character it
 will be automatically added in the \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ code.

 @note This tag is used in the generated output file (`.tex`).
 \sa  \ref cfg_makeindex_cmd_name "MAKEINDEX_CMD_NAME" for the part in the `Makefile` / `make.bat`.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='COMPACT_LATEX' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c COMPACT_LATEX tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen generates more compact
 \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ documents. This may be useful for small projects and may help to
 save some trees in general.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='PAPER_TYPE' defval='a4' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c PAPER_TYPE tag can be used to set the paper type that is used
 by the printer.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name='a4' desc='(210 x 297 mm)'/>
      <value name='letter' desc='(8.5 x 11 inches)'/>
      <value name='legal' desc='(8.5 x 14 inches)'/>
      <value name='executive' desc='(7.25 x 10.5 inches)'/>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXTRA_PACKAGES' format='string' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c EXTRA_PACKAGES tag can be used to specify one or more \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$
 package names that should be included in the \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ output. The package
 can be specified just by its name or with the correct syntax as to be used with the
 \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ `\usepackage` command.

 To get the `times` font for instance you can specify :
\verbatim
  EXTRA_PACKAGES=times
or
  EXTRA_PACKAGES={times}
\endverbatim
 To use the option `intlimits` with the `amsmath` package you can specify:
\verbatim
   EXTRA_PACKAGES=[intlimits]{amsmath}
\endverbatim
 If left blank no extra packages will be included.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LATEX_HEADER' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_HEADER tag can be used to specify a user-defined \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$
 header for the generated \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ document.
 The header should contain everything until the first chapter.
 If it is left blank Doxygen will generate a
 standard header.

 It is highly recommended to start with a default header using
\verbatim
doxygen -w latex new_header.tex new_footer.tex new_stylesheet.sty
\endverbatim
 and then modify the file \c new_header.tex.

 See also section \ref doxygen_usage for information on how to generate
 the default header that Doxygen normally uses.

 <br>Note: Only use a user-defined header if you know what you are doing!

 @note The header is subject to change so you typically
 have to regenerate the default header when upgrading to a newer version of
 Doxygen.
 The following commands have a special meaning inside the header (and footer):
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs doxywizard='0' doxyfile='0'>
<![CDATA[
 <dl>
 <dt><code>$title</code><dd>will be replaced with the project name.
 <dt><code>$datetime</code><dd>will be replaced with the current date and time.
 <dt><code>$date</code><dd>will be replaced with the current date.
 <dt><code>$time</code><dd>will be replaced with the current time.
 <dt><code>$year</code><dd>will be replaces with the current year.
 <dt><code>$showdate(<format>)</code><dd>will be replaced with the current date
           and time according to the format as specified by `<format>`. The
           `<format>` follows the rules as specified for the
           \ref cmdshowdate "\\showdate" command with the exception that no `)`
           is allowed in the `<format>`.
 <dt><code>$doxygenversion</code><dd>will be replaced with the version of Doxygen
 <dt><code>$projectname</code><dd>will be replaced with the name of
           the project (see \ref cfg_project_name "PROJECT_NAME")
 <dt><code>$projectnumber</code><dd>will be replaced with the project number
           (see \ref cfg_project_number "PROJECT_NUMBER")
 <dt><code>$projectbrief</code><dd>will be replaced with the project brief
           description (see \ref cfg_project_brief "PROJECT_BRIEF")
 <dt><code>$projectlogo</code><dd>will be replaced with the project logo
           (see \ref cfg_project_logo "PROJECT_LOGO")
 <dt><code>$latexdocumentpre</code><dd>will be replaced by an output language dependent setting
           e.g. embed the entire document in a special environment (for Chinese, Japanese etc.)
           Commonly used together with `$latexdocumentpost` in the footer.
 <dt><code>$latexdocumentpost</code><dd>will be replaced by an output language dependent setting
           e.g. embed the entire document in a special environment (for Chinese, Japanese etc.)
           Commonly used together with `$latexdocumentpre` in the header.
 <dt><code>$generatedby</code><dd>will be replaced with the output language dependent
           version of the text "Generated by" or when the
           \ref cfg_timestamp "TIMESTAMP" is set by the output language
           dependent version of the text &quot;Generated on `$datetime` for `$projectname` by&quot;.
 <dt><code>$latexcitereference</code><dd>will be replaced by the output language dependent$
           version of the word "Bibliography".
           This setting is typically used in combination with the block name `CITATIONS_PRESENT`.
 <dt><code>$latexbibstyle</code><dd>will be replaced with the latex bib style to be used as
           set by \ref cfg_latex_bib_style "LATEX_BIB_STYLE", in case nothing is set the bib style
           `plain` is used.
           This setting is typically used in combination with the block name `CITATIONS_PRESENT`.
 <dt><code>$latexbibfiles</code><dd>will be replaced by the comma separated list of `bib`. files
           as set by \ref cfg_cite_bib_files "CITE_BIB_FILES" (when necessary a missing `.bib` is
           automatically added).
           This setting is typically used in combination with the block name `CITATIONS_PRESENT`.
 <dt><code>$papertype</code><dd>will be replaced by the paper type as set in
           \ref cfg_paper_type "PAPER_TYPE" and the word "paper" is directly appended to it to have
           a correct \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ paper type.
 <dt><code>$langISO</code><dd>will be replaced by the ISO language name.
 <dt><code>$languagesupport</code><dd>will be replaced by an output language dependent setting
           of packages required for translating terms of the specified language.
 <dt><code>$latexfontenc</code><dd>will be replaced by an output language dependent setting
           of the fontencoding to be used.
           This setting is typically used in combination with the block name `LATEX_FONTENC`.
 <dt><code>$latexfont</code><dd>will be replaced by an output language dependent setting
           of the fonts to be used.
 <dt><code>$latexemojidirectory</code><dd>will be replaced by the directory as set in
           \ref cfg_latex_emoji_directory "LATEX_EMOJI_DIRECTORY" with the backslashes replaced by
           forward slashes (so usable by \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$). In case the
           \ref cfg_latex_emoji_directory "LATEX_EMOJI_DIRECTORY" is
           empty, the current directory will be used.
 <dt><code>$makeindex</code><dd>will be replaced by the command as set in
           \ref cfg_latex_makeindex_cmd "LATEX_MAKEINDEX_CMD". Then the command doesn't start with
           a backslash, a backslash is automatically prepended. In case the setting is empty the
           command `\makeindex` is used.
 <dt><code>$extralatexpackages</code><dd>will be replaced by commands for using the packages set
           in \ref cfg_extra_packages "EXTRA_PACKAGES".
 <dt><code>$extralatexstylesheet</code><dd>will be replaced by commands for using the packages set
           in \ref cfg_latex_extra_stylesheet "LATEX_EXTRA_STYLESHEET" (when the extension is the default
           extension, `.sty`, this extension is stripped for the package name).
 <dt><code>$latexspecialformulachars</code><dd>will be replaced by the code for some special
           unicode characters that are commonly used (i.e. superscript minus, superscript 2 and superscript 3)
 <dt><code>$formulamacrofile</code><dd>will be replaced by the name of the file as set
           in \ref cfg_formula_macrofile "FORMULA_MACROFILE".
           This setting is typically used in combination with the block name `FORMULA_MACROFILE`.
 </dl>

To cope with differences in the layout of the header and footer that depend on
 configuration settings, the header and footer can also contain special blocks that
 will be copied to the output or skipped depending on the configuration.
 Such blocks have the following form:
\verbatim
 %%BEGIN BLOCKNAME
 Some context copied when condition BLOCKNAME holds
 %%END BLOCKNAME
 %%BEGIN !BLOCKNAME
 Some context copied when condition BLOCKNAME does not hold
 %%END !BLOCKNAME
\endverbatim
The following block names are set based on the used settings in the
 configuration file:
 <dl>
 <dt><code>COMPACT_LATEX</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when the \ref cfg_compact_latex "COMPACT_LATEX" option is enabled.
 <dt><code>PDF_HYPERLINKS</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when the \ref cfg_pdf_hyperlinks "PDF_HYPERLINKS" option is enabled.
 <dt><code>USE_PDFLATEX</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when the \ref cfg_use_pdflatex "USE_PDFLATEX" option is enabled.
 <dt><code>LATEX_BATCHMODE</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when the \ref cfg_latex_batchmode "LATEX_BATCHMODE" option is enabled.
 <dt><code>TIMESTAMP</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when the \ref cfg_timestamp "TIMESTAMP" option is enabled.
 </dl>
The following block names are set based on the fact whether or not the tag has a
 value in the used configuration file:
 <dl>
 <dt><code>LATEX_FONTENC</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when the Doxygen latex translator function returns a value for the font encoding
     to be used. It is to be used in combination with the above mentioned `$latexfontenc`.
 <dt><code>FORMULA_MACROFILE</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when the \ref cfg_formula_macrofile "FORMULA_MACROFILE" option is not empty. It is
     to be used in combination with the above mentioned `$formulamacrofile`.
 </dl>
The following block name is set based on whether or not a feature is used in the
 documentation:
 <dl>
 <dt><code>CITATIONS_PRESENT</code><dd>Content within this block is copied to the output
     when in the documentation citations are present and the relevant .. are present.
     It is to be used in combination with the above mentioned `$latexcitereference`,
     `$latexbibstyle` and `$latexbibfiles`.
 </dl>
]]>
      </docs>
      <docs documentation='0'>
<![CDATA[
 For a description of the possible markers and block names see the documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LATEX_FOOTER' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_FOOTER tag can be used to specify a user-defined \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ footer for
 the generated \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ document. The footer should contain everything after
 the last chapter. If it is left blank Doxygen will generate a
 standard footer.

 See \ref cfg_latex_header "LATEX_HEADER" for more information on
 how to generate a default footer and what special commands can be
 used inside the footer.

 See also section \ref doxygen_usage for information on how to generate
 the default footer that Doxygen normally uses.

 Note: Only use a user-defined footer if you know what you are doing!
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='LATEX_EXTRA_STYLESHEET' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_EXTRA_STYLESHEET tag can be used to specify additional
 user-defined \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ style sheets that are included after the standard
 style sheets created by Doxygen. Using this option one can overrule
 certain style aspects. Doxygen will copy the style sheet files to
 the output directory.
 \note The order of the extra style sheet files is of importance (e.g. the last
 style sheet in the list overrules the setting of the previous ones in the list).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='LATEX_EXTRA_FILES' format='file' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_EXTRA_FILES tag can be used to specify one or more extra images
 or other source files which should be copied to the \ref cfg_latex_output "LATEX_OUTPUT"
 output directory.
 Note that the files will be copied as-is; there are no commands or markers
 available.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='PDF_HYPERLINKS' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c PDF_HYPERLINKS tag is set to \c YES, the \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ that
 is generated is prepared for conversion to PDF (using \c ps2pdf or \c pdflatex).
 The PDF file will
 contain links (just like the HTML output) instead of page references.
 This makes the output suitable for online browsing using a PDF viewer.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='USE_PDFLATEX' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c USE_PDFLATEX tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will use the engine
 as specified with \ref cfg_latex_cmd_name "LATEX_CMD_NAME"
 to generate the PDF file directly from the \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$
 files.  Set this option to \c YES, to get a higher quality PDF documentation.
<br>
 See also section \ref cfg_latex_cmd_name "LATEX_CMD_NAME" for selecting the engine.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='LATEX_BATCHMODE' defval='NO' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_BATCHMODE tag signals the behavior of \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ in case of an error.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="NO" desc='same as ERROR_STOP' />
      <value name="YES" desc='same as BATCH' />
      <value name="BATCH" desc='In batch mode nothing is printed on the terminal, errors are scrolled as if \&lt;return\&gt; is hit at every error; missing files that TeX tries to input or request from keyboard input (\\read on a not open input stream) cause the job to abort' />
      <value name="NON_STOP" desc='In nonstop mode the diagnostic message will appear on the terminal, but there is no possibility of user interaction just like in batch mode' />
      <value name="SCROLL" desc='In scroll mode, TeX will stop only for missing files to input or if keyboard input is necessary' />
      <value name="ERROR_STOP" desc='In errorstop mode, TeX will stop at each error, asking for user intervention' />
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='LATEX_HIDE_INDICES' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c LATEX_HIDE_INDICES tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will not
 include the index chapters (such as File Index, Compound Index, etc.)
 in the output.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LATEX_BIB_STYLE' format='string' defval='plain' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_BIB_STYLE tag can be used to specify the style to use for the
 bibliography, e.g. \c plainnat, or \c ieeetr.
 See https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BibTeX and \ref cmdcite "\\cite"
 for more info.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='LATEX_EMOJI_DIRECTORY' format='dir' defval='' depends='GENERATE_LATEX'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c LATEX_EMOJI_DIRECTORY tag is used to specify the (relative or absolute)
 path from which the emoji images will be read.
 If a relative path is entered, it will be relative to the \ref cfg_latex_output "LATEX_OUTPUT"
 directory. If left blank the \ref cfg_latex_output "LATEX_OUTPUT" directory will be used.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='RTF' docs='Configuration options related to the RTF output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_RTF' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_RTF tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will generate RTF output.
 The RTF output is optimized for Word 97 and may not look too pretty with
 other RTF readers/editors.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='RTF_OUTPUT' format='dir' defval='rtf' depends='GENERATE_RTF'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c RTF_OUTPUT tag is used to specify where the RTF docs will be put.
 If a relative path is entered the value of \ref cfg_output_directory "OUTPUT_DIRECTORY" will be
 put in front of it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='COMPACT_RTF' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_RTF'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c COMPACT_RTF tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen generates more compact
 RTF documents. This may be useful for small projects and may help to
 save some trees in general.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='RTF_HYPERLINKS' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_RTF'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c RTF_HYPERLINKS tag is set to \c YES, the RTF that is generated
 will contain hyperlink fields. The RTF file will
 contain links (just like the HTML output) instead of page references.
 This makes the output suitable for online browsing using Word or some other
 Word compatible readers that support those fields.

 <br>Note: WordPad (write) and others do not support links.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='RTF_STYLESHEET_FILE' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_RTF'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Load stylesheet definitions from file. Syntax is similar to Doxygen's
 configuration file, i.e. a series of assignments. You only have to provide
 replacements, missing definitions are set to their default value.
<br>
 See also section \ref doxygen_usage for information on how to generate
 the default style sheet that Doxygen normally uses.

]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='RTF_EXTENSIONS_FILE' format='file' defval='' depends='GENERATE_RTF'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set optional variables used in the generation of an RTF document.
 Syntax is similar to Doxygen's configuration file.
 A template extensions file can be generated using
 <code>doxygen -e rtf extensionFile</code>.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='RTF_EXTRA_FILES' format='file' depends='GENERATE_RTF'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c RTF_EXTRA_FILES tag can be used to specify one or more extra images
 or other source files which should be copied to the \ref cfg_rtf_output "RTF_OUTPUT"
 output directory.
 Note that the files will be copied as-is; there are no commands or markers
 available.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Man' docs='Configuration options related to the man page output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_MAN' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_MAN tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 generate man pages for classes and files.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='MAN_OUTPUT' format='dir' defval='man' depends='GENERATE_MAN'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MAN_OUTPUT tag is used to specify where the man pages will be put.
 If a relative path is entered the value of \ref cfg_output_directory "OUTPUT_DIRECTORY" will be
 put in front of it.
 A directory \c man3 will be created inside the directory specified by
 \c MAN_OUTPUT.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='MAN_EXTENSION' format='string' defval='.3' depends='GENERATE_MAN'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MAN_EXTENSION tag determines the extension that is added to
 the generated man pages. In case
 the manual section does not start with a number, the number 3 is prepended.
 The dot (.) at the beginning of the \c MAN_EXTENSION tag is optional.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='MAN_SUBDIR' format='string' defval='' depends='GENERATE_MAN'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MAN_SUBDIR tag determines the name of the directory created within \c MAN_OUTPUT
 in which the man pages are placed. If defaults to man followed by \c MAN_EXTENSION
 with the initial . removed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='MAN_LINKS' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_MAN'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c MAN_LINKS tag is set to \c YES and Doxygen generates man output,
 then it will generate one additional man file for each entity documented in
 the real man page(s). These additional files only source the real man page,
 but without them the \c man command would be unable to find the correct page.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='XML' docs='Configuration options related to the XML output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_XML' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_XML tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 generate an XML file that captures the structure of
 the code including all documentation.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='XML_OUTPUT' format='dir' defval='xml' depends='GENERATE_XML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c XML_OUTPUT tag is used to specify where the XML pages will be put.
 If a relative path is entered the value of \ref cfg_output_directory "OUTPUT_DIRECTORY" will be
 put in front of it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='XML_PROGRAMLISTING' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_XML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c XML_PROGRAMLISTING tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 dump the program listings (including syntax highlighting
 and cross-referencing information) to the XML output. Note that
 enabling this will significantly increase the size of the XML output.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='XML_NS_MEMB_FILE_SCOPE' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_XML'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c XML_NS_MEMB_FILE_SCOPE tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen
 will include namespace members in file scope as well, matching the HTML
 output.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Docbook' docs='Configuration options related to the DOCBOOK output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_DOCBOOK' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
If the \c GENERATE_DOCBOOK tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will generate Docbook files
that can be used to generate PDF.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOCBOOK_OUTPUT' format='dir' defval='docbook' depends='GENERATE_DOCBOOK'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
The \c DOCBOOK_OUTPUT tag is used to specify where the Docbook pages will be put.
If a relative path is entered the value of \ref cfg_output_directory "OUTPUT_DIRECTORY" will be put in
front of it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='AutoGen' docs='Configuration options for the AutoGen Definitions output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_AUTOGEN_DEF' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_AUTOGEN_DEF tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 generate an AutoGen Definitions (see https://autogen.sourceforge.net/) file
 that captures the structure of the code including all
 documentation. Note that this feature is still experimental
 and incomplete at the moment.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Sqlite3' docs='Configuration options related to Sqlite3 output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_SQLITE3' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
If the \c GENERATE_SQLITE3 tag is set to \c YES Doxygen will generate a
\c Sqlite3 database with symbols found by Doxygen stored in tables.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='SQLITE3_OUTPUT' format='dir' defval='sqlite3' depends='GENERATE_SQLITE3'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
The \c SQLITE3_OUTPUT tag is used to specify where the \c Sqlite3 database will be put.
If a relative path is entered the value of \ref cfg_output_directory "OUTPUT_DIRECTORY" will be
put in front of it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SQLITE3_RECREATE_DB' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_SQLITE3'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
The \c SQLITE3_RECREATE_DB tag is set to \c YES, the existing doxygen_sqlite3.db
database file will be recreated with each Doxygen run.
If set to \c NO, Doxygen will warn if a database file is already found and not modify it.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>

  </group>
  <group name='PerlMod' docs='Configuration options related to the Perl module output'>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_PERLMOD' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_PERLMOD tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 generate a Perl module file that captures the structure of
 the code including all documentation.
 <br>Note that this
 feature is still experimental and incomplete at the
 moment.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='PERLMOD_LATEX' defval='0' depends='GENERATE_PERLMOD'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c PERLMOD_LATEX tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will generate
 the necessary \c Makefile rules, \c Perl scripts and \f$\mbox{\LaTeX}\f$ code to be able
 to generate PDF and DVI output from the Perl module output.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='PERLMOD_PRETTY' defval='1' depends='GENERATE_PERLMOD'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c PERLMOD_PRETTY tag is set to \c YES, the Perl module output will be
 nicely formatted so it can be parsed by a human reader.  This is useful
 if you want to understand what is going on. On the other hand, if this
 tag is set to \c NO, the size of the Perl module output will be much smaller
 and Perl will parse it just the same.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='PERLMOD_MAKEVAR_PREFIX' format='string' defval='' depends='GENERATE_PERLMOD'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The names of the make variables in the generated `doxyrules.make` file
 are prefixed with the string contained in \c PERLMOD_MAKEVAR_PREFIX.
 This is useful so different `doxyrules.make` files included by the same
 `Makefile` don't overwrite each other's variables.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Preprocessor' docs='Configuration options related to the preprocessor'>
    <option type='bool' id='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c ENABLE_PREPROCESSING tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
 evaluate all C-preprocessor directives found in the sources and include
 files.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='MACRO_EXPANSION' defval='0' depends='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c MACRO_EXPANSION tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will expand all macro
 names in the source code. If set to \c NO, only conditional
 compilation will be performed. Macro expansion can be done in a controlled
 way by setting \ref cfg_expand_only_predef "EXPAND_ONLY_PREDEF" to \c YES.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXPAND_ONLY_PREDEF' defval='0' depends='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXPAND_ONLY_PREDEF and \ref cfg_macro_expansion "MACRO_EXPANSION" tags are both set to \c YES
 then the macro expansion is limited to the macros specified with the
 \ref cfg_predefined "PREDEFINED" and \ref cfg_expand_as_defined "EXPAND_AS_DEFINED" tags.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SEARCH_INCLUDES' defval='1' depends='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SEARCH_INCLUDES tag is set to \c YES, the include files
 in the \ref cfg_include_path "INCLUDE_PATH" will be searched if a \c \#include is found.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='INCLUDE_PATH' format='dir' depends='SEARCH_INCLUDES'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c INCLUDE_PATH tag can be used to specify one or more directories that
 contain include files that are not input files but should be processed by
 the preprocessor.

 Note that the \c INCLUDE_PATH is not recursive, so the setting of \ref cfg_recursive "RECURSIVE" 
 has no effect here.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='INCLUDE_FILE_PATTERNS' format='string' depends='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 You can use the \c INCLUDE_FILE_PATTERNS tag to specify one or more wildcard
 patterns (like `*.h` and `*.hpp`) to filter out the header-files in the
 directories. If left blank, the patterns specified with \ref cfg_file_patterns "FILE_PATTERNS" will
 be used.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='PREDEFINED' format='string' depends='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c PREDEFINED tag can be used to specify one or more macro names that
 are defined before the preprocessor is started (similar to the `-D` option of
 e.g. \c gcc). The argument of the tag is a list of macros of the form:
 <code>name</code> or <code>name=definition</code> (no spaces).
 If the definition and the \c "=" are omitted,  \c "=1" is assumed. To prevent
 a macro definition from being undefined via \c \#undef or recursively expanded
 use the <code>:=</code> operator instead of the \c = operator.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='EXPAND_AS_DEFINED' format='string' depends='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \ref cfg_macro_expansion "MACRO_EXPANSION" and
 \ref cfg_expand_only_predef "EXPAND_ONLY_PREDEF" tags are set to \c YES then
 this tag can be used to specify a list of macro names that should be expanded.
 The macro definition that is found in the sources will be used.
 Use the \ref cfg_predefined "PREDEFINED" tag if you want to use a different macro definition that
 overrules the definition found in the source code.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='SKIP_FUNCTION_MACROS' defval='1' depends='ENABLE_PREPROCESSING'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c SKIP_FUNCTION_MACROS tag is set to \c YES then
 Doxygen's preprocessor will remove all references to function-like macros that are alone
 on a line, have an all uppercase name, and do not end with a semicolon.
 Such function macros are typically
 used for boiler-plate code, and will confuse the parser if not removed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='External' docs='Configuration options related to external references'>
    <option type='list' id='TAGFILES' format='file'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c TAGFILES tag can be used to specify one or more tag files.

For each
tag file the location of the external documentation should be added. The
format of a tag file without this location is as follows:
\verbatim
  TAGFILES = file1 file2 ...
\endverbatim
Adding location for the tag files is done as follows:
\verbatim
  TAGFILES = file1=loc1 "file2 = loc2" ...
\endverbatim
where `loc1` and `loc2` can be relative or absolute paths or URLs.
 See the section \ref external for more information about the use of tag files.

 \note
  Each tag file must have a unique name
  (where the name does \e NOT include the path).
  If a tag file is not located in the directory in which Doxygen
  is run, you must also specify the path to the tagfile here.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='GENERATE_TAGFILE' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When a file name is specified after \c GENERATE_TAGFILE, Doxygen will create
 a tag file that is based on the input files it reads.
 See section \ref external for more information about the usage of
 tag files.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='ALLEXTERNALS' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c ALLEXTERNALS tag is set to \c YES, all external classes and namespaces 
 will be listed in the class and namespace index. 
 If set to \c NO, only the inherited external classes will be listed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTERNAL_GROUPS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTERNAL_GROUPS tag is set to \c YES, all external groups will be listed
 in the topic index. If set to \c NO, only the current project's groups will
 be listed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='EXTERNAL_PAGES' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c EXTERNAL_PAGES tag is set to \c YES, all external pages will be listed
 in the related pages index. If set to \c NO, only the current project's
 pages will be listed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
  </group>
  <group name='Dot' docs='Configuration options related to diagram generator tools'>
    <option type='bool' id='HIDE_UNDOC_RELATIONS' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If set to \c YES the inheritance and collaboration graphs will hide
 inheritance and usage relations if the target is undocumented
 or is not a class.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='HAVE_DOT' defval='0'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If you set the \c HAVE_DOT tag to \c YES then Doxygen will assume the \c dot tool is
 available from the \c path. This tool is part of
 <a href="https://www.graphviz.org/">Graphviz</a>, a graph
 visualization toolkit from AT\&T and Lucent Bell Labs. The other options in
 this section have no effect if this option is set to \c NO
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='DOT_NUM_THREADS' defval='0' minval='0' maxval='32' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DOT_NUM_THREADS specifies the number of \c dot invocations Doxygen is
 allowed to run in parallel. When set to \c 0 Doxygen will
 base this on the number of processors available in the system. You can set it
 explicitly to a value larger than 0 to get control over the balance
 between CPU load and processing speed.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOT_COMMON_ATTR' format='string' depends='HAVE_DOT'
      defval='fontname=Helvetica,fontsize=10'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 \c DOT_COMMON_ATTR is common attributes for nodes, edges and labels of subgraphs.
 When you want a differently looking font in the dot files that Doxygen generates
 you can specify fontname, fontcolor and fontsize attributes.
 For details please see
 <a href=https://graphviz.org/doc/info/attrs.html>Node, Edge and Graph Attributes specification</a>
 You need to make sure dot is able to find the font,
 which can be done by putting it in a standard location
 or by setting the \c DOTFONTPATH environment variable or by
 setting \ref cfg_dot_fontpath "DOT_FONTPATH" to the
 directory containing the font.
 Default graphviz fontsize is 14.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOT_EDGE_ATTR' format='string' depends='HAVE_DOT'
      defval='labelfontname=Helvetica,labelfontsize=10'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 \c DOT_EDGE_ATTR is concatenated with \ref cfg_dot_common_attr "DOT_COMMON_ATTR".
 For elegant style you can add 'arrowhead=open, arrowtail=open, arrowsize=0.5'.
 <a href=https://graphviz.org/doc/info/arrows.html>Complete documentation about arrows shapes.</a>
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOT_NODE_ATTR' format='string' depends='HAVE_DOT'
      defval='shape=box,height=0.2,width=0.4'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 \c DOT_NODE_ATTR is concatenated with \ref cfg_dot_common_attr "DOT_COMMON_ATTR".
 For view without boxes around nodes set 'shape=plain' or 'shape=plaintext'
 <a href=https://www.graphviz.org/doc/info/shapes.html>Shapes specification</a>
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOT_FONTPATH' format='dir' defval='' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 You can set the path where \c dot can find font specified with
 fontname in \ref cfg_dot_common_attr "DOT_COMMON_ATTR" and others dot attributes.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='CLASS_GRAPH' defval='YES'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c CLASS_GRAPH tag is set to \c YES or \c GRAPH or \c BUILTIN then Doxygen
 will generate a graph for each documented class showing the direct and
 indirect inheritance relations.
 In case the \c CLASS_GRAPH tag is set to \c YES or \c GRAPH and \ref cfg_have_dot "HAVE_DOT" is
 enabled as well, then `dot` will be used to draw the graph.
 In case the \c CLASS_GRAPH tag is set to \c YES and \ref cfg_have_dot "HAVE_DOT" is disabled
 or if the \c CLASS_GRAPH tag is set to \c BUILTIN, then the built-in generator will be used.
 If the \c CLASS_GRAPH tag is set to \c TEXT the direct and indirect inheritance relations
 will be shown as texts / links.
 Explicit enabling an inheritance graph or choosing a different representation for an inheritance graph
 of a specific class, can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdinheritancegraph "\\inheritancegraph".
 Disabling an inheritance graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhideinheritancegraph "\\hideinheritancegraph".
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="NO" bool_representation="NO" />
      <value name="YES" bool_representation="YES" />
      <value name="TEXT" bool_representation="YES" />
      <value name="GRAPH" bool_representation="YES" />
      <value name="BUILTIN" bool_representation="YES" />
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='COLLABORATION_GRAPH' defval='1' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c COLLABORATION_GRAPH tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
 will generate a graph for each documented class showing the direct and
 indirect implementation dependencies (inheritance, containment, and
 class references variables) of the class with other documented classes.
 Explicit enabling a collaboration graph, when \c COLLABORATION_GRAPH is set to \c NO, can be
 accomplished by means of the command \ref cmdcollaborationgraph "\\collaborationgraph".
 Disabling a collaboration graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhidecollaborationgraph "\\hidecollaborationgraph".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GROUP_GRAPHS' defval='1' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GROUP_GRAPHS tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen
 will generate a graph for groups, showing the direct groups dependencies.
 Explicit enabling a group dependency graph, when \c GROUP_GRAPHS is set to \c NO, can be
 accomplished by means of the command \ref cmdgroupgraph "\\groupgraph".
 Disabling a directory graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhidegroupgraph "\\hidegroupgraph".

 See also the chapter \ref grouping "Grouping" in the manual.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='UML_LOOK' defval='0' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c UML_LOOK tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will generate inheritance and
 collaboration diagrams in a style similar to the OMG's Unified Modeling
 Language.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='UML_LIMIT_NUM_FIELDS' defval='10' minval='0' maxval='100' depends='UML_LOOK'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \ref cfg_uml_look "UML_LOOK" tag is enabled, the fields and methods are shown inside
 the class node. If there are many fields or methods and many nodes the
 graph may become too big to be useful. The \c UML_LIMIT_NUM_FIELDS
 threshold limits the number of items for each type to make the size more
 manageable. Set this to 0 for no limit. Note that the threshold may be
 exceeded by 50% before the limit is enforced. So when you set the threshold
 to 10, up to 15 fields may appear, but if the number exceeds 15, the
 total amount of fields shown is limited to 10.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='DOT_UML_DETAILS' defval='NO' depends='UML_LOOK'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
If the \c DOT_UML_DETAILS tag is set to \c NO, Doxygen will
show attributes and methods without types and arguments in the UML graphs.
If the \c DOT_UML_DETAILS tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
add type and arguments for attributes and methods in the UML graphs.
If the \c DOT_UML_DETAILS tag is set to \c NONE, Doxygen will not generate
fields with class member information in the UML graphs.
The class diagrams will look similar to the default class diagrams but using
UML notation for the relationships.
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name="NO" />
      <value name="YES" />
      <value name="NONE" />
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='DOT_WRAP_THRESHOLD' defval='17' minval='0' maxval='1000' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DOT_WRAP_THRESHOLD tag can be used to set the maximum number of characters to display on
 a single line. If the actual line length exceeds this threshold significantly it will be wrapped
 across multiple lines. Some heuristics are applied to avoid ugly line breaks.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='TEMPLATE_RELATIONS' defval='0' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c TEMPLATE_RELATIONS tag is set to \c YES then
 the inheritance and collaboration graphs will show the relations between templates and their instances.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INCLUDE_GRAPH' defval='1' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c INCLUDE_GRAPH, \ref cfg_enable_preprocessing "ENABLE_PREPROCESSING" and
 \ref cfg_search_includes "SEARCH_INCLUDES"
 tags are set to \c YES then Doxygen will generate a graph for each documented file
 showing the direct and indirect include dependencies of the file with other
 documented files.
 Explicit enabling an include graph, when \c INCLUDE_GRAPH is is set to \c NO, can be
 accomplished by means of the command \ref cmdincludegraph "\\includegraph".
 Disabling an include graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhideincludegraph "\\hideincludegraph".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INCLUDED_BY_GRAPH' defval='1' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c INCLUDED_BY_GRAPH, \ref cfg_enable_preprocessing "ENABLE_PREPROCESSING" and
 \ref cfg_search_includes "SEARCH_INCLUDES"
 tags are set to \c YES then Doxygen will generate a graph for each documented file
 showing the direct and indirect include dependencies of the file with other
 documented files.
 Explicit enabling an included by graph, when \c INCLUDED_BY_GRAPH is set to \c NO, can be
 accomplished by means of the command \ref cmdincludedbygraph "\\includedbygraph".
 Disabling an included by graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhideincludedbygraph "\\hideincludedbygraph".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='CALL_GRAPH' defval='0' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c CALL_GRAPH tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will
 generate a call dependency graph for every global function or class method.
 <br>Note that enabling this option will significantly increase the time of a run.
 So in most cases it will be better to enable call graphs for selected
 functions only using the \ref cmdcallgraph "\\callgraph" command.
 Disabling a call graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhidecallgraph "\\hidecallgraph".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='CALLER_GRAPH' defval='0' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c CALLER_GRAPH tag is set to \c YES then Doxygen will
 generate a caller dependency graph for every global function or class method.
 <br>Note that enabling this option will significantly increase the time of a run.
 So in most cases it will be better to enable caller graphs for selected
 functions only using the \ref cmdcallergraph "\\callergraph" command.
 Disabling a caller graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhidecallergraph "\\hidecallergraph".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GRAPHICAL_HIERARCHY' defval='1' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GRAPHICAL_HIERARCHY tag is set to \c YES then
 Doxygen will graphical hierarchy of all classes instead of a textual one.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='DIRECTORY_GRAPH' defval='1' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c DIRECTORY_GRAPH tag is set
 to \c YES then Doxygen will show the dependencies a directory has on other directories
 in a graphical way. The dependency relations are determined by the \c \#include
 relations between the files in the directories.
 Explicit enabling a directory graph, when \c DIRECTORY_GRAPH is set to \c NO, can be
 accomplished by means of the command \ref cmddirectorygraph "\\directorygraph".
 Disabling a directory graph can be accomplished by means of the command
 \ref cmdhidedirectorygraph "\\hidedirectorygraph".

]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='DIR_GRAPH_MAX_DEPTH' minval='1' maxval='25' defval='1' depends='DIRECTORY_GRAPH'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DIR_GRAPH_MAX_DEPTH tag can be used to limit the maximum number of
 levels of child directories generated in directory dependency graphs by \c dot.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='enum' id='DOT_IMAGE_FORMAT' defval='png' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DOT_IMAGE_FORMAT tag can be used to set the image format of the images
 generated by \c dot. For an explanation of the image formats see the section output formats
 in the documentation of the \c dot tool
 (<a href="https://www.graphviz.org/">Graphviz</a>).
 \note If you choose \c svg you need to set
 \ref cfg_html_file_extension "HTML_FILE_EXTENSION" to \c xhtml in order to make the SVG files
 visible in IE 9+ (other browsers do not have this requirement).
]]>
      </docs>
      <value name='png'/>
      <value name='jpg'/>
      <value name='gif'/>
      <value name='svg'/>
      <value name='png:gd'/>
      <value name='png:gd:gd'/>
      <value name='png:cairo'/>
      <value name='png:cairo:gd'/>
      <value name='png:cairo:cairo'/>
      <value name='png:cairo:gdiplus'/>
      <value name='png:gdiplus'/>
      <value name='png:gdiplus:gdiplus'/>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='INTERACTIVE_SVG' defval='0' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If \ref cfg_dot_image_format "DOT_IMAGE_FORMAT" is set to \c svg, then this option can be set to \c YES to
 enable generation of interactive SVG images that allow zooming and panning.
 <br>Note that this requires a modern browser other than Internet Explorer.
 Tested and working are Firefox, Chrome, Safari, and Opera.
 \note For IE 9+ you need to set \ref cfg_html_file_extension "HTML_FILE_EXTENSION" to \c xhtml in order
 to make the SVG files visible. Older versions of IE do not have SVG support.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DOT_PATH' format='filedir' defval='' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DOT_PATH tag can be used to specify the path where the \c dot tool can be found.
 If left blank, it is assumed the \c dot tool can be found in the \c path.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='DOTFILE_DIRS' format='dir' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DOTFILE_DIRS tag can be used to specify one or more directories that
 contain dot files that are included in the documentation (see the
 \ref cmddotfile "\\dotfile" command).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='DIA_PATH' format='dir' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
You can include diagrams made with dia in Doxygen documentation. Doxygen will then run
dia to produce the diagram and insert it in the documentation. The DIA_PATH tag allows
you to specify the directory where the dia binary resides. If left empty dia is assumed
to be found in the default search path.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='DIAFILE_DIRS' format='dir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DIAFILE_DIRS tag can be used to specify one or more directories that
 contain dia files that are included in the documentation (see the
 \ref cmddiafile "\\diafile" command).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='PLANTUML_JAR_PATH' format='filedir' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When using PlantUML, the \c PLANTUML_JAR_PATH tag should be used to specify the path where
 java can find the \c plantuml.jar file or to the filename of \c jar file to be used.
 If left blank, it is assumed PlantUML is not used or
 called during a preprocessing step. Doxygen will generate a warning when it encounters a
 \ref cmdstartuml "\\startuml" command in this case and will not generate output for the diagram.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='PLANTUML_CFG_FILE' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When using PlantUML, the \c PLANTUML_CFG_FILE tag can be used to specify a configuration
 file for PlantUML.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='PLANTUML_INCLUDE_PATH' format='dir' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 When using PlantUML, the specified paths are searched for files specified by the \c !include
 statement in a PlantUML block.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='PLANTUMLFILE_DIRS' format='dir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c PLANTUMLFILE_DIRS tag can be used to specify one or more directories that
 contain PlantUml files that are included in the documentation (see the
 \ref cmdplantumlfile "\\plantumlfile" command).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='DOT_GRAPH_MAX_NODES' minval='0' maxval='10000' defval='50' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c DOT_GRAPH_MAX_NODES tag can be used to set the maximum number of
 nodes that will be shown in the graph. If the number of nodes in a graph
 becomes larger than this value, Doxygen will truncate the graph, which is
 visualized by representing a node as a red box. Note that if the number
 of direct children of the root node in a graph is already larger than
 \c DOT_GRAPH_MAX_NODES then the graph will not be shown at all. Also note
 that the size of a graph can be further restricted by \ref cfg_max_dot_graph_depth "MAX_DOT_GRAPH_DEPTH".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='int' id='MAX_DOT_GRAPH_DEPTH' minval='0' maxval='1000' defval='0' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MAX_DOT_GRAPH_DEPTH tag can be used to set the maximum depth of the
 graphs generated by \c dot. A depth value of 3 means that only nodes reachable
 from the root by following a path via at most 3 edges will be shown. Nodes
 that lay further from the root node will be omitted. Note that setting this
 option to 1 or 2 may greatly reduce the computation time needed for large
 code bases. Also note that the size of a graph can be further restricted by
 \ref cfg_dot_graph_max_nodes "DOT_GRAPH_MAX_NODES". Using a depth of 0 means no depth restriction.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='DOT_MULTI_TARGETS' defval='0' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 Set the \c DOT_MULTI_TARGETS tag to \c YES to allow dot to generate multiple output
 files in one run (i.e. multiple -o and -T options on the command line). This
 makes \c dot run faster, but since only newer versions of \c dot (>1.8.10)
 support this, this feature is disabled by default.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='GENERATE_LEGEND' defval='1' depends='HAVE_DOT'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 If the \c GENERATE_LEGEND tag is set to \c YES Doxygen will
 generate a legend page explaining the meaning of the various boxes and
 arrows in the dot generated graphs.
 \note This tag requires that \ref cfg_uml_look "UML_LOOK" isn't set, i.e. the
 Doxygen internal graphical representation for inheritance and collaboration diagrams
 is used.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='bool' id='DOT_CLEANUP' defval='1'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
If the \c DOT_CLEANUP tag is set to \c YES, Doxygen will
remove the intermediate files that are used to generate the various graphs.
 <br>Note:
This setting is not only used for dot files but also for msc temporary files.
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='string' id='MSCGEN_TOOL' format='file' defval=''>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 You can define message sequence charts within Doxygen comments using the \ref cmdmsc "\\msc"
 command. If the \c MSCGEN_TOOL tag is left empty (the default), then Doxygen will use a built-in
 version of mscgen tool to produce the charts.
 Alternatively, the \c MSCGEN_TOOL tag can also specify the name an external tool.
 For instance, specifying `prog` as the value, Doxygen will call the tool
 as `prog -T <outfile_format> -o <outputfile> <inputfile>`. The external tool
 should support output file formats "png", "eps", "svg", and "ismap".
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='list' id='MSCFILE_DIRS' format='dir'>
      <docs>
<![CDATA[
 The \c MSCFILE_DIRS tag can be used to specify one or more directories that
 contain msc files that are included in the documentation (see the
 \ref cmdmscfile "\\mscfile" command).
]]>
      </docs>
    </option>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='USE_WINDOWS_ENCODING'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='DETAILS_AT_TOP'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='QTHELP_FILE'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='QTHELP_CONFIG'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='DOXYGEN2QTHELP_LOC'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='int' id='MAX_DOT_GRAPH_WIDTH'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='int' id='MAX_DOT_GRAPH_HEIGHT'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='CGI_NAME'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='CGI_URL'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='DOC_URL'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='DOC_ABSPATH'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='BIN_ABSPATH'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='list' id='EXT_DOC_PATHS'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='USE_INLINE_TREES'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='SHOW_DIRECTORIES'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='HTML_ALIGN_MEMBERS'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='int' id='SYMBOL_CACHE_SIZE'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='XML_SCHEMA'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='XML_DTD'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='PERL_PATH'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='MSCGEN_PATH'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='list' id='TCL_SUBST'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='int' id='COLS_IN_ALPHA_INDEX'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='enum' id='OUTPUT_TEXT_DIRECTION'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='DOCBOOK_PROGRAMLISTING'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='RTF_SOURCE_CODE'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='LATEX_SOURCE_CODE'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='CLASS_DIAGRAMS'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='int' id='DOT_FONTSIZE'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='string' id='DOT_FONTNAME'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='FORMULA_TRANSPARENT'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='DOT_TRANSPARENT'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='HTML_TIMESTAMP'/>
    <option type='obsolete' orgtype='bool' id='LATEX_TIMESTAMP'/>
  </group>
  <generator>
    <message name='minmaxdef'><![CDATA[<br/> Minimum value: {0}, maximum value: {1}, default value: {2}.]]></message>
    <message name='minmaxdefcode'><![CDATA[ Minimum value: <code>{0}</code>, maximum value: <code>{1}</code>, default value: <code>{2}</code>.]]></message>
    <message name='possible'><![CDATA[Possible values are: ]]></message>
    <message name='defvaltxt'><![CDATA[The default value is: {0}.]]></message>
    <message name='defvalcode'><![CDATA[The default value is: <code>{0}</code>.]]></message>
    <message name='sysdep'><![CDATA[system dependent]]></message>
    <message name='defdir'><![CDATA[The default directory is: <code>{0}</code>.]]></message>
    <message name='deffile'><![CDATA[The default file is: <code>{0}</code>.]]></message>
    <message name='deffileabs'><![CDATA[The default file (with absolute path) is <code>{0}</code>]]></message>
    <message name='deffilefull'><![CDATA[The file has to be specified with full path.]]></message>
    <message name='defimg'><![CDATA[The default image is: <code>{0}</code>.]]></message>
    <message name='defimgabs'><![CDATA[The default image (with absolute path) is <code>{0}</code>]]></message>
    <message name='defimgfull'><![CDATA[The image has to be specified with full path.]]></message>
    <message name='depstxt'><![CDATA[This tag requires that the tag \ref cfg_{0} "{1}" is set to \c YES.]]></message>
    <message name='andtxt'><![CDATA[ and ]]></message>
  </generator>
</doxygenconfig>
